[{"id":1,"question":"Ferrum phosphoricum 12X, Lithium carbonicum 12X, Natrum sulphuricum 30X, Nux vomica 30X, Rhododendron chrysanthum 6X, Spiraea ulmaria 12X","answer":"Ipomopsis havardii (A. Gray) V.E. Grant","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-03-09 11:38:45","box":2},
{"id":2,"question":"Simethicone","answer":"Viscum L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-02-20 03:18:06","box":3},
{"id":3,"question":"Vitamin- Mineral Omega-3 Supplement","answer":"Baltimora recta L.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKFSURBVBgZBcHLi1V1HADwz+/cc1/j2Az4qiYjhQoXIg5lr11tWgi5aWWLwB64FMJdu5Ya/QVFbkKiNrVKMAmipLI2UZJMZcmMM+k8LnPnnnPP+X37fNLHX9y4mHM6Pa7zoGoAABAAQLdk0PXRG6cWz0GZI7128oWD+waDQUqpAwAAACaZtpn6/Oqt13EOynGV+/3+IF26tm7inlG66dCBVcPupiay+1tDv96aMxNHlPZ459VD2pwSQFk3FEVHkaiLFYf2rur3/rZZjTRto+z3HT74kD+Xdpnv7ZUzAFBCRlEkVazpdddt7Gyq2om6aTSxrd/v266G9gwLIRAASsgoUhJNVrVTk6ayM63UudFmpKnIrbJIIgIAlBBBkZKBfUbby6LTtfzbebv7jOtGOdszk3es/Dfy/qd/yNGZO3Phelz9+c4zJURQFMlsZ8GdlbvmBst2xhMvnnjSK4uzvvz+X++ePgIALl1bk3O6XgQiKIpktrvfw8Pj1n9ZN66m7o8acOXHuwAmDVsVaxu1lLISIrh57y1tztqcPVGtWe4lnWDaZhfPLso5BDrCTElVVba2a2VESHh58RyAztENP3xVmFRT713+S5Fo2iy3WSAiCGa6WZlAAIB2OK/JoWobnaKLkLRSSiKHiKxppuq6UQ66aVOezh078CwpCRBG4590U+nsyd2aXKMgiJQNyp4Ln9x2b2tb2SvT5c++XnqubuNoBABtjrmOrmzHhzfetnfmUUlhbfyPN5/+QGFgXNXKM6eOnwcAgG9ufhePPciB2ZGXjp0w31ugYGOyYP+uxkyPMiUpIgAAwFNnr3z7+CPD5+f78wblA5o8lXKWopXT2O+3l6xuTf0PNZJB+2NWN98AAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAF5SURBVDjLpZMxa5RBEIafvdu7RPCMhYLBxCoiaqO/IHZWNvkBooh1WrHUwk4s0sTGQrsQwf9gK1gpQoJoY++d5Ludd2YtvlwuaWLODAyzsPu88zLMplorp4n85t3W5vLS4sPc6/VqgMKxIiRRJEoRxYzx2NpajFKMvaaxH993X+flpcXHl169SAv3P/Gge42Nm2//2TUlOH/ubO/p85eXc879dHF1lfmrXe50bgNwfeXKsQJfd37S7XZw95TNxa+7a8Aa94BxKXz+sgOA5JgJuWNyJEfe1m+7gUvkGsGtGyv/NcDt9x8uZCkA2GvGM8Fn5ueIGmR3B2Cu3z/yoNbaJpWI9uwR1NreAXgEuZhmAicJEO5kk2YGD5qFTx1EjRODk4gIsu0LuMeJwSMCxexgIIfhduPSsQI1gjwajYZN0wx+D/8QEfsC00kfdjMxVKn0cwcPV1p/8mx9MFh4BJ1BcU23T0JmyA1JuBlyx2WEO2Y2jPCP6bTf+S96U2WlbWXHPgAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2023-05-15 22:12:36","box":1},
{"id":4,"question":"Pecan Carya illinoensis","answer":"Galium ambiguum W. Wight ssp. ambiguum","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJcSURBVDjLpZPtT5JhFMafrW997I9rscA+FFu2QRurtlw5cQ4InLpwBogIPNFSiNJ4C+JVkj0QTBHQKFPQlJfwlanY1tXz3ARkn2jd27Wz++yc33XOvd0UAOp/RNGR/X5zeH9rOlTDVKAK3fsqJrxlqN27GHPuYHh+G4rXRQzZNjEws47Hli/oo/PxNsAU3qvWT3/gX3TPuHrWBhiC30nSktXDtKLB1NI4NKkxqBMqjDByPFkcxNBCPwbCfXgUeEBq705m0AZM+qsk2e3hau88W+4ANOy+XPLFQrkrcbW31KkOYJx9rBaAOzPR0gVHW6x593q9cDgcqB6e4sZoogMYdXzD0ck5ZhfLsHGKVfAqVoadKcMdzcLr82PuwwZCoRACgQCWVzdhoK2gaVpDAMNzWzhkAXamQpze/I4t13w+j2AwiFwuh7W1NXg8HmQyGSgUCshkssuU3F7AQf0c84kK3n68KFc4hXQ6DavVCqlUCqVSSdaIx+NQq9UGMsHg7Ab2jxtwp5rOvqUqia3CUqnEObWn0mp1KBaLcLlckMvloPpfrhOAl230/SGLxQK3241CoQC9Xg9nskKk1emQzWZZkBZCoRBU3/NP2GMBgXTTObjSjI1GA8lkEgzDwO/3E4iObXY6nYhEIhCJRHoWcIW6b1pF7egMlYNT7NROUKzU8XX3GJ+3D2E0GgmAm4Zbh2s0mUyIRqMcAGKx+BIlMeSiYu1K/fbEMm4+TaFnJIHrSgZX5TFIZNPo7e1Fj9QOs9kMlUqFaw9pCASCnzwe7x15xG6/rUQiAZ/Px9/5XyhZOMVGKlOdAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2023-03-08 13:36:08","box":7},
{"id":5,"question":"Propranolol Hydrochloride","answer":"Astragalus laxmannii Jacq. var. robustior (Hook.) Barneby & S.L. Welsh","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKbSURBVBgZBcFNiFVlGADg5/vOuffOdcb5cbKcjUn5V7poFJEiKMKybDYFgdSmKAiiokW1aNHSXWQQuGwR2KJFq2hTkFqUEbZRMzQIJS1nbPxjnHvvOd/b86SI8OSHx1/uT/ZeyslujCGBhEhE0ZTy5/Vr8V26ufzeiSMLQ4AUEQ4c+vHE52/tfiDnNB1UAoAICIu3R47+et0/FwcrZ0+fW/fDkYUB1JCrtK1bV9NnrqpySiSi0EbRNOHOqPX4lrX2bq2dLItromxffuzNr2eOffrsIENKaSIiqm6VdTJ1ospUiZTIEoq5ya6FPXM2be7168nxz6De+c7vhx+a39h/48tF8zN9nYqfrtyx956+4aj49swVMxPTtsyuc+9EpdepbXp41rGf/3oBL+ZmEKfunqiNBfv3TDl+acXqMDyxa8rlxaEUvH5gvQvXkpMXG9+fX9HrVFKdG8iKX26sFM/vGFen7PbSsq29WpWT01eW7Ns2Z02v0utWxrqVsW5HyKQM6mht7lX8duGOj7+5ZPv96y3913r/i8sU9j86Y9QGKUttEjkURAB1jMq4YClluWV6NUlTterSooN7N8opqasgEkFI2kJbgBxDvWiTs+evOvTKg/qdZDgqbq0Uj+yaBEmSIqlzUuVkrJO0TYC6jGKuSnSa0O9mf1weuNHe9PTWDUqEErSFQAki0amyZtiAOrVp6tz5qw6/ep8miqlOdnG59cy+WSWAKlOhkxMoEUaDAvKFr3Z+MBhdX51eW4PXDm7wyds7AAAAQJQwWm1AhmZQSlNKAAAAAADUdS5NWxqoYbTa/jvere6SRuMRkQUFMNWvQQT9TpaS0qnSrbYpf0MNKcVHT717/LmU0nyINQCCQAggwGop5VSdHYX/AYn4JwmEykruAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-03-18 19:29:57","box":3},
{"id":6,"question":"Cephalexin","answer":"Oxalis incarnata L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-03-19 20:04:02","box":4},
{"id":7,"question":"Oxaprozin","answer":"Senna pendula (Humb. & Bonpl. ex Willd.) Irwin & Barneby var. glabrata (Vogel) Irwin & Barneby","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAIMSURBVDjLjZO9apVBEIaf2f2iRxMJUfEHFEStBCtRC0sLSzsbEcFCrQQVL0AvQAgkd2FhZyOkNRAsrERQRMFwonDM/35nd/a1OCfHRKI4MEwx7LMvM++YJADM7ARwFIj8O5aAL5IqAJIYQi6klH7mnL2Uot0ypaSZmZlp4BQQJO0AXMo5+9ramtbX10e5vLysXq+nbrerUooWFxc1Ozs7gjRD+TasIcZICIFaK7nCSomkYlAinQydiUlu3rr9IDZjdv/e3ecmaQtwsZQyv9F3Pq8ZH1eNzSzGGzEenA4txw8eYH+ETgNjASb2Npeb7dNZ+A5vfzTkKvYE6EQIDgEjhDGWeqvsC06jwvEjhwEYAR6+/PBo7pshREDkAKVCFQwQYBGMQCdGNot+A57O5ye56noqQgwa0USJRqngMg7vNcZiZLNAJbDSH3zcPFuoU1n2uHWFKDEAi2hw/iCcnTTOTRm1DjbmLlYzpKHypnVdzc5Uv4IJXKIKbpwxrhyz0XzMDEnEGJkM4lAz6DV953TfZX2HiihVXDsZuHLMtvwxMpyZUWvdYcsmuazvCn2XXIPBnRjf6d3toBDCjl5oXbQOrWOtQ3Lx6msdyd6qf+Y2AL3WZcnFpotUxJtuZfqd//XxEFABQip6nQYqLLlIDq2LF5+cO3OZ9z3tdpHV3TcAt23nfHJ4zoH/CweWfgFQJVPOGSHTggAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJtSURBVDjLpZPNS5RRFMZ/7zgzWmqTFpObMiuyKDOFCoJaCUKKUFAUBRKtWrSpoP8gwk1BixbpppURtIigqAjKkgSp0KJP86NGbaYZpxmd9773ve89LTTKj1bdxblw4Pmd53Kf44gI/3PCADJyT0z+ByIaMT4S+IjRiPGQwANfERiFGBd8RezQDWc+IDBEth9dRBcBB+YKIDB169hiB142wTIRxLqzXQdELOAg/CE4oWLEd5d4gjFYPYnJ94H1ENGzt9VgFWIVYl2iqw9i/cISgMADDGIViD8n+lusEFvATfaTLq4ie+eizPx4gqMS7WEAM52etTxvsou1ag7ionPDeD+XU1V3glhNA9nhWt4/6OwIA9hAoT71YLzPEGgQQ6BylFTHEVtA58agpIHK+C4yQ++IOpryFVWUrVoXCwMEbhqTS1C28zhgsXqU/KubSFDAn/kGxTuI1TTjTXQTXe4w+vo9vtJp5U7vDQE4IvjJAaYenScofILAx4qPl/+KhLcS29iCGr+OE5kiUlZOSWHou5+baNp15vbH0O//Lt/djp9NkX16GSs+mfQ42m4htqkNlbhGKOKjc+tJPn6OzhdaG88+fA0QAsAonKIQpY2nELOSsftd2JV7iG9rQU92UhQVvFw1qWf9RFJ9bD7X178gB4qp+1cQoxhLZihrbMNInInBq1TEo6jMWjJPewinX2K1mpcDZ+Ey3epoksOnu/jQfZ7xkV6K19VjkqnximhRc92FF28Wxj20sPHh86TRb+9SU7+P0tJaEv2D08rVB5YSL+ngyP5Kt3HDmvDurTVIxOt1k6mTrZcGvvxrnX8BwNty8Brb9FgAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-03-28 18:48:15","box":6},
{"id":8,"question":"Irbesartan and Hydrochlorothiazide","answer":"Astragalus miser Douglas ex Hook. var. tenuifolius (Nutt.) Barneby","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAK5SURBVDjLjZBbSNNxHMVXDz3UQ0892AVSs4Q0shQRA5uzCFGL5Rxqc1u5mZpNnWNN533eaDr976blZeFllc7mMLMl6IOGqdOpS4vAPaRbb6FiQjpPm5QahvmFw5cfP87nezgkAKS9JI4+zp5Wey3Ot57AnMZ9rYnn0RAV6HHoz/+eZl74SYq12d2x0OaGnapL9azeF6CBeYxY6PSHrZeDH8OVsOmCsaA9BYva8/u+AKroo5V2cy8Wh1RYMz/D8nsV5id60F/sZ90XgBoew51pydxYmuyAY7YTKxY97AMEihKu6v4J4JK92Ep26CLBIEPFoqwl033HCGHqT7uOj69dhbAbcjFY+wAXOOd7AgQ+R/4CMIPPUJTsMEd1PBk71SjjQV4nQYUiF/lSAbo+tqCkvwi+eec0F/lnD28BZPRLg0+Sb6Gz4B5m2sRo5dNAMCioTQpDk1kM9bgQVaYMlJsy0f6pAen6NAQlB6i2AAq6Z/uXfu2uwrTZZMjGH6HCJEDxaDpyRlMg+pACtoqFOVXU/wurKI6GYkKEfMN9pKvjwK26ibjSUFAl12B7GrENOHi5RqQQpe0qzIeWBW5dDArb2ei2KGG2GSF7lwK6zBcMoffrTfOB4OeJVL5peeAbUPpSh9xGLQSEBvUjqxAo5hFfcn29a7oaXTMEXCPt40DWl4TAVLdVknt4LY3G614xzDogmQE4I0DCABDTDdC1ADEEROT4ocdSj51jmFK6ACBNSfzXxzrk4L+yg9kLMPUbiNdugKZxIFINRModuPLwNB4b76LMyNo0l71lbSew1oTYOkoyEJs3DK4RYL9xJtADDANwx5WifA6xvCjclnqj0pi4edm1XW8nQEr63JwU1FNEzQ6ktej900dBzptyahpk8SRCsk3wvPHCKs9KLEgQehuchiVX7N+73NXfL+Zkqi9OGtlWAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-10-02 10:31:29","box":5},
{"id":9,"question":"Doxycycline hyclate","answer":"Eriogonum thurberi Torr.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAHnSURBVDjLpZM/a1RRFMTPfXv3L5sYIXYSxMbCWsTCOo1JGlPYWKeyshE7v4JNwCZfQRBBBBsLERsbv4K1hGz23TMz91i8t4muleQ0h1vM3B/MnBQRdpVJz78c3Y8wq5KJMlJGyOg0OAyrXbr9/tmnr38a5IjYFOtnUUawE+NvkZfVGw/XCTIhE5Ums/GL0WRklZckWCM5P1vuHBzvPuhJXvUGNEJpPB3d8sLXgoYEh6IGdGYAGc4Gjrw4XbbD0eA7Ch5fEMBpdCY4Ex2T2cb0TcQ4VSqRSiQToUSnTefTiailt37t4Hj3GxyWUWBwNMTY4Byb2Z2zX4uXVdoi61zSlqg5wZkv/UatsShLH1iynyjYz966oSMwFI4IWUS9LdWNKm0ImhEYwzV050xSeMHALBovsFzajgAFqRSfEDSx3hQ1AzShYwTnAI4BWh+SGnoLC4uKQusJcK9dtNuL0+XdzetzK63vEMwXwi7GhAITa+PFI8IqHJbfHn34aGZ2eLL3pMnNDxRYlYogEWzgSl0KNDgrnIHOgAQtr+LoSR5569ae+7YXJDhq/3ugIAAanQFnNTMQtLR+C4cnewHHOxQEHOGFtTOg4BBBsaMLUU/zejUvSMpllVf3QO+r3re1Sv8S/O80dsX5DaeOJ5G2UDDRAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJpSURBVDjLfVLPTxNREP52C+mvbSKE2FYkkIiJioo9KMT0QKImnAwHPXjk1IPoxUsPaoiaSDw0MTEe/Cs4mWhVLGCDlWgwFCMJiYeCSGstu9ttt/vLeS9dLBCc5MvMezvzzcz3VnAcB8ys2xMOTp2GmU7DMU04lgXbMGA3ffvoKJw37xF8+0pAi7W5QWuR01Jos3vXNwzstX8EhslJbF3nyZyI+WbcdgCBuENAHx0qRm8vLEZCYN6q1yH098PWapTT+M8EDeNBvV6/X752HWpIQt3jgcFGVxT4Sr8RnplFiHIOJFi7d7fgaJra2d0t+ehs2zZcgYkYnz0eVbs8Urixh0BgSSsrK0OmaU6Hw+GIQh1rtRonYBBFEV6vlyOTyWzquj6WSCQ+7tKARk12dXVFZFmGpmmw6AUYGAFbQ1VVfh+LxSI0TXKfiJQUZ5OwziZTvdmdwSWrVqsIBoOgCeL7Vshms1ZPT49YLBZ5EVo0cM/5nzl8L36BrFWgaNtKRS0/efl46REXsUHP4ya3ejdeWs+iJH7DSPwCjnYex0x+OrSwPPdweOLIIb4CjVXe+aWbu7vjM//pxzucOzEIS7QwGL0CSzAwfOYiS7/pEsyz/ZnSbtdWlORfaBckXD15ize5c+kFjh0+y0Kf2HznqcXFxU2fz4dAILBLA0EQIKsV5DeymEqP829Tr8extvWVl3omJycxMDCwnsvl5NXV1fPRaFTq6OiAJElcdb/fj4r8h3SYRV+4DyWtgO3qFj4szUGu6E8Fd3dmqVRqiNZJkqhxQicTl564TJhfRlrRBXWM0kIEhfB84dlG8i8v6tBqmkd4owAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2024-08-11 08:43:45","box":2},
{"id":10,"question":"One Seed Juniper","answer":"Cucurbita pepo L. var. pepo","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJsSURBVBgZfcFLbExhGIDh9z9zztw6marQUm1DNZEQEdUpsRC2lLgsJDZNGmFjY2nBErGzENewIEUQRBBBJFW3IC6xqqYSd4tWtOPMnMv/fdqYUIvxPEZVqWbn6sUzm+tyV3OpTMFaQUET2eSN7YdvdFHhUMWudR1OY23NxVwyXbAiWFUiK8YfLa3ZvXFpDxUOVbTUanZKpmZ5Jl9L67w5NDY1IKKICHWZzAkqXKpI6seoftZsae/a7Ez3ikwoaZox63H/7LGACocq9n3fE06dlh3L4hOaFMbLMiH48FTntjWGVLgD1wt+Oj8/Y4zDX8r5rZ/ibYcWvjxV09/R3NJKyXh4JuTDx2HtHVrU28lvZuBap7ateYQxBpRxih9Ydhx4QuvceRQKAU9vncWYNF4yT1NHN6eP3olvv3q/JX7cc8EMXC5I29o+E349jA0T4OTZ2xtRmrqaKZ2zGCyCtfzhKkxDeXHuXvDm7etNLpFBJcSGSVSUn0MP6M6/gvg4PKSq45uupA4+33PJxaiRuMTo0CDRyCckKlO3YD0/2nfxL2VCzoPRk8v4kpxJ86IVSZfIwc3UM2PVfkBAFRuHJL7f5KtfxqqlZBP4McQ2orlhCQaIn70ojXj9sUukqC0TfjsJKL8JKbFkyTEmSYwYPBWsRLgEWCDR0d40Z2XfiEsAKjEYQBUQkAhHIxrcH9QbHzVF1CmiDJPOtPMOOLOSEca5hIrBgiqoBQ1RCUDKqJZQ66O2iMajqPUBYTJXQyH2h5HYA3VAE6h6IClUakAjVEMwITgxtlxmMlfLweehIxsaUBwMhv9RwNwF0WEqfgE9XTQvEQ+I/gAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-09-28 09:21:14","box":4},
{"id":11,"question":"Meniscus 6","answer":"Penstemon hallii A. Gray","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKRSURBVDjLzZHfS5NRGMeFoIsCoX/CEpq6GeWNGypO24/WpuliQ0hf3dyQta3lvGkibthgpF4kFYkI3igKIoleSCmiEDUVf5ZMk4Eazr0nXU3n3n07Z3eL7rrpwBcenuf7fM7znJMFIOtflPV/AFLuJwaqYyrCJLgcRHDYSLLFSi6aTSTBNZDzujpypn9I4lXV5JdKE4nJ7xrTANpQQxXD9BSwsACsrADb28DGBoQP7xEZGkJ0cBAnAwPgX71GuLsb4WcenErLYidFxRoG+IS3b4CJCWBkBFhfB5aXgdFRCC4XwmYz9jkO0YYGHBmN+KxWY6urC9s2O4j4TpgB8lNPHR9Tz30AvQ17e0if2VkI1dXYVyrxXaHAD6qd0lJser3Y4ZpA8m8f8LnimvQb0H2v0X0nhXYPMD4OHBwAS0tIGQyI0EaeQvjKSoR8Puw+4kDyboWiNwoKMn7hwtyUnaivf5dsbQUWF4G1NaTo6KS8HLGKChz5/fhGm/mbhaHo9TzRX7/xzGDMjjyomZp6bEeANvT398NP3+FrZyc2W2zwO5xJlvN6vVGLxeKSSqVXMwASieRylUrV3dPTg8PDQ4RCIfoUs3jh8eCl2SJ82dpKsNz8/DyYR6VS+TMAYrH4ntPpJMHVVbTf1/1U090bGxvR29uLtra2dKxUKpN6vX6SQZj3zwn8HR0dcQZYLiouLJfKkjMzMwgGg5ibm6M/OwqZTHaq0WiuMADzZgBEIlGzyWTiGUCn002XlJQk5HI5tFptWixmOVZjAObNAOTSo1arNwOBAD88PHw8NjaGvr4+2O12uN3udMxyrMY8zJsByMnJuURHLFAoFLscx8WsVmuc6ry2traOqozGJyzHaszDvL8B+W6qBSeP34AAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-09-14 06:28:18","box":3},
{"id":12,"question":"allopurinol","answer":"Allium haematochiton S. Watson","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJcSURBVDjLfVI7aJpRFD7/7y8qdlDwQdQYwQYJJdCSNmSwlBQcQjK4Zil0KIUgXVwFUeji1Lk4dLGh7RCoDhYtRQoODnUqjVY0SJKKT3zg83/03Jv+YlLMhcO595zzffe8GEmSQD7CK580sztgmkgAtYsiSETwTrTq4ADg23fQfv3CyBgOFo7E8/NgGTgnkYmms0UIsNcIZvwVQBCoDDY24PzwcP6mJLcSoFOaToFdX6eAhtsNo50dGJpMwLpcAOMx9d9GEGYuLkHhcICwtQW91VXQ6/XQ2N0Fbm0NxF+/acxSAtXx+yBc/gnDWRXaSGBaWQGdTgc1ux3E0xJIxXJY9/NHcBHDkMbk83kNz/MuFMVsNgPHh08vzx67X9i2H9GgWq0G0vHH+On9zRDxT7EM1A2/31+lBLlc7lypVFoFrBtJqJDUWZaFyWQCHMdBvV6HZrNJgNTf6/Wg3W4/o2NE49FoNIpZrdY7JOVutwvD4ZAK+YAQm81mcDqdoFKpyIdQqVQ+I+6EkRcplUrdRUPCYrG41Go19Pt9CqSzRyE2EceYTCYFjAuGQqHX15ro8XhKWNvDYrF4QtJUKBQUIP5bICyRgNsYsyeD/5uC1+sdYECq1WpRAtIDohmGoSTYj0E4HE4tHSM5GLRvMBhoylqtFndnTBtK7qjt2PnNpQTRaFSDGTy12WxQrVYhHo+XMpnMu2w2C51OBxy4YFje/lICBD8xGo0arJV0+i2+HwSDweeFQmEvFotdkH7cJOBupG8tl8sVBB4FAoGkbI9EIkmfz3cvnU6/wR3YXsT8BaM2jDnYpij1AAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-05-02 08:14:20","box":2},
{"id":13,"question":"isosorbide dinitrate","answer":"Plumbago indica L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-04-01 12:44:44","box":3},
{"id":14,"question":"Asterias rubens, Bryonia alba, Conium maculatum Galium aparine, Hoang-nan, Lachesis, Ledum palustre, Nux Vomica, Ova tosta and Viscum album.","answer":"Penstemon angustifolius Nutt. ex Pursh var. vernalensis N.H. Holmgren","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-10-03 00:44:45","box":6},
{"id":15,"question":"Lidocane and Phenylephrine HCL","answer":"Medeola virginiana L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-02-20 16:25:23","box":7},
{"id":16,"question":"Ziprasidone hydrochloride","answer":"Bryobrittonia longipes (R.S. Williams) Horton","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAQAAAC1+jfqAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAChSURBVCjPY/zPgB8wMVCqgAVEFP7/w/CH4TcY/gLh59ul9oLtdmZk+I8D7vn/4f+e//8hJqT/h+kGwqu/GA7oQIz/D7NiJiM22/8j3BD9/xdMPwQ+vyL1n+EfEEIVLGXEph9Jge9/JN1XfzPcAbrhH8NfhILNWEz4h2yCPZIJYP88fyf1D9mRB7G6AUmBAdQXYN1X/zB8AYfDebACRopjEwDsBmruXDxiUwAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKgSURBVDjLY/j//z8DJRhMmJQd+x89/W4IRQbY1x5L8590dzmy5PuIqC4gfvA+PPIyEMfhNqD06H+L9gfG9p33/jr23OMEiX30DTj8yT/oFxCf+hAYfBeIfwPxIyBWwjSg5Mh/tYZHzDr1D34aND7Y9tXOsf2Lg/O/z85uNjCFn908lT56eH985xXwzXvygwYUA4yLD/9Xcm+QlS572JWesP7XVyOL79/MLKci22Rc/6DXvPH+X8um+79t2u7/tOu4/w9ugFHxof8wha+1LP89NHT9iaxZIf/BCpWie7/Vi+/N/25kqvrN2Oz/suiO6QgDig6ADfgtJrX0p6TMb1u/Xd+5Eh9M4k16yCyQdH+HYOK9H6JJd+tgBv7U0j3wXVvvA9wAg8J9/6sNAvT/8gr++8Mn1MYQ8aCFIfzBf6bwB3+Zwx/8Ywu7H44e+j8VVX4hDMjf+/8/I6v/fya2OyghHHCn3GuRw3TvJTZnumq0n+4OFHi9x4nl305X5kfXDHmvwg3Qz9v9/ycDS8hvBhZxmGavmZZeHjMtX3jMMn/QW6p5+XyJxd/vW3v//7u24//XFUX/T2fr/tnlzJILVqyXu/P/HFENB5hmxw6jaY6dRh8dugwXOfQY8ux0Yb77Daj5/yTf///LBf//b1P8/7rL4T9Q/B5Yg2729v+WJTqSFqXaM81LdR8B6bcWZToZMANBzv53dt1/ZPC+XuI/SBxiQNa2/0YZmv6GGepu6gGWrkAanBqFNTxkQTTQz4+/zE3+/x+o6UcZw/93QPwwg/k/UPwJ2ADtzC3/tTM2/9fK2ATEG/9rpW0A4vX/NUE4dd3/sriU/8dS1P8/K1f8/6qS9f/dFMb/u33Z/u9wZa4iOtcdCZetANp4HxoLj0GaQeIAMa12DZDYXzMAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-06-19 16:43:10","box":6},
{"id":17,"question":"TITANIUM DIOXIDE, OCTINOXATE, ZINC OXIDE","answer":"Setaria P. Beauv.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKvSURBVDjLpVNNTxNRFD1vZtoZICkyhdYilFQ0QKSayoJEoyY10UTjgh0LUXcuJW5wSYwfG1caNCxY8RPQxOBHEDEkREJSS2qpIKHWllLol+10pp0Z3xsCupPEl9x3J5N7zj3v3Fximib+5wjsGh8ff1ipVILVarVO13WiqqpNURQ7y4ZhEFEUNVmWX46MjAyz+qGhoT6avk9OTu6QsbGxRp7nc4FAAEwNBVgRWXqDG9eOQ1ubwNP33XC4e7CyEruZzWafUbCDBpPez3d2doZ7e3tlt9uNeDyOVCqFTCaDVm83Zha3EC2exqm+cyCEIJlMDnAcJ0qSBEEQSKFQOC/QrsccDgfC4TBcLhf8fj/oU0CfgpaWFkQiEczNzcHpdCIYDGJzcxO5XM6qiUajXQIrTKfTaG5uRrXBiyfvFJRqBAbVJxIbLrQdhVwsUvkrYCoZMBaLwePxWE/l2FUqldDe3o6pLxpUk4Nko2HnoHM2fPjRYAG3t7ctsKZpoAbvqxQYAXXbil+6nQJ5CBx1iFpE6KWZdtAJWcHArI59s2wpYCx7rOyYprELpiQcDZ4jKJfLVs3fCvYI9hVQR2E361AzJHBsQuauCjsU5PN59JEEvK9H4c38RBcvIp4+ifk9AsYYCoUQaPVjKe+CKkjg6dhshoIj2jKwOIWrPh49F+9A9J2AEprG8se3WNvIQ2DdWQc2Hmc2i36fzzKHyS1S9xnxwNZndF+/D2l1Bph9gPrGQ/B1dOBMJAaBznR4fX39MVUiNjU1kYWFBcIImDKWqWGm7FCJdNgHXLn7ZwdGPaCDZ0b/e5mmLwnxs4O32ho2XkFVUijTf8UCj6+rSHAH2bh62T2xPD9bS1bqUOBtyO4QfEsQnbZ+Tg66zp8GvfdKOz9v8zrp0HkzQVEvLk/XHv0Gq/ySugg7yEwAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-05-22 18:46:55","box":1},
{"id":18,"question":"ATORVASTATIN CALCIUM","answer":"Isoetes piedmontana (N.E. Pfeiffer) C.F. Reed","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAQAAAC1+jfqAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAADwSURBVCjPpdGhSwNhHMbxX93f8WpRs/VAGXYF0SA4DgyGsaDBwdQfJoO23dzumsFgfoNcMEwss3gKr0G4uuzSC6dfy8KdDBHkU79PegT5nfw5SEiIiRnQp0dEJdCaBgmO4ZQjYi/YrU0DDXVyVVlHdDlhe7IRIqL1AU/kMww5YK0ummWM6cww5oHNd1FfUDDi44dHCgpaX3KMx3NLzqgk5xqPp4G0cTh6vHFf4rjE4QiQQ1JSLnjlruSFM1JSFpAWFksXRTmiSYN1VlmhicUyj+x/3mBRzitOWcISY5Cwv5NtVdbLLGIwzGGeTVv+/eY3onJlSlwTV9MAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-09-11 08:34:36","box":3},
{"id":19,"question":"Metoclopramide Hydrochloride","answer":"Penstemon concinnus D.D. Keck","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAMESURBVDjLXZNrSFNxGMYPgQQRfYv6EgR9kCgKohtFgRAVQUHQh24GQReqhViWlVYbZJlZmZmombfVpJXTdHa3reM8uszmWpqnmQuX5drmLsdjenR7ev9DR3Xgd3h43+d5/pw/HA4AN9zITSPUhJ14R0xn87+h2ZzJvZVInJpzAQOXQOQMt+/5rvhMCLXv9Vjrt1rSXitmwj+Jua1+Ox+2HfGNdGf6yW8l5sUKPNVcRsiaPDA22Ahv6/7Ae/0aKdviQ0G7B/c6f8Zg+gbfh079Mjno0MhS58lflOsgEjh3BXc+bM/0DzbvDwj314znt/bjof0HdPw3FBq6kP+oCxVNfdDZvqPsrQmf6zdFRtyPJgbrFoqUTeS+FnPrekpmiC2lS+QcUx+qrf0wmFzodYfgC0nwhoYh9oegfdmLsmYXHj7JhV23erS7ZNYHyibGLiLtXsO19BoHSiwu6Ok09gwFg/gy8BO/STOkKFBk7EWh2YkLeh5Hy4Ws2B2w157iDvOpxw4UPRPRTSfL41FIsow7ZeXwUFF4dBQ1L96A/xLEFf1HMC/LxAt25PH+VN0HXH1gh2dEwdBoBGO0OKvW4L7hCdIvavBSsMIRVHCi0ArmZZl4wbYrz/yHSq1Ql9vQLylUEoE7GMal3OuxMG/7CO848N6n4HheK5iXZeIFmy88Nu+8aYJG24G3ziB+0Ee7wwqemlvQ5w9hcAJwyUDtpwBOFLeBeVkmXpB0qlK9RV2HlLsCsvUivHRhQwoQjhCkA1TgJX1OK0JVzIN5WSZesPZ44XKia+P5BqSS4aq+BzZXABLdhyQrsJPOqv4MVcEbMA/zsky8gLHyYO7hI9laecOZWuzLfYXU2zzSblmQerMZqjwTknOeY9dlIw5kVcrMG/8XpoQgCEkOhwNNJn5i7bFSrFDpsCrFEIPpLacr0WxpibYIQpS86/8pMBqNswnJ6XSivqHBv3R3pmbxzgwz4Z+EaTXtwqIogrzjxIJ4QVVV1UyihxgjFv3/K09Bu/lEkBgg5rLZH+fT5dvfn7iFAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAL9SURBVDjLddN9MNNxHAfw31/Vf6LoLq4HRVdxpaurDnEdESepUxTCJVe5U52eyFNFp9iMeS5n19ZankZu2q3IUOZh2WweaiOnyeSI8tBF775bl0vmj++fr+/78/l8vx8KALXUUTDpyzqYtF1dLHr0YJOoWvNWKFVw0lr5Ab4clqtjJG3bRguDsDObvkKZw/BXZjNaZEzabBc7B70CNsZ6lRj7IENXaR4Ytpt/3TE3bl+Mc+imnbkZdIJnx9VKaFtEGGx4jh4eDd3P0qGVv8Gw/C0UHBri1xp/W4CVzDQPZRa9U80rwJBEAG2zEFPDn6CuzEdbeiQaEwJRF3sKfTWl0DSLwD9tNzOPO+j3PDsyUlV9/EJM9CuhEZdhUtuPbpI8M6pFK+MKqs85oOSYNarDXdBfVwlpfvxPPZalJK6UpSaVq0vy8LmxAgMiDqZHNOhkJaHuqifkBQlQV7P1mOdtBe4RK4iiTqLxfsRPqi3++nLp3diMtqS4uXG1XI+/D/ZCxc8lA2vHu+xoVPhtn8dPvDaB7WmF4kBHJFqYTlKSG5d9JDFRfR946fqyp79ooChMwKsIZ9Tf8oeqqmgBfnzYEmUhzuD62eP8mpUjVENk+IN2Rize81Ix/K5WPzBdsjTrBvgnti7CLHdLkn5Ah+fC1hg1UuLLwbWyzBjIc66hJSUMr6M8ybQDDCaz3DaiJMgJT/wdQPBkqJnRBUolYA8pHt2GJDkE4ptHIQx3NJxMcKHrBjwNcNThOYKbg8yMllOqF5yv2vYG1Mf5QRC8G+W+Wwxjl/XgkdKz3e1A8ATBoboXpJroUaNaqRgfa8ogOGtvEBe5b9bjzEM7dHiAYN+//4fKXLda+b7iITQSEdRCLirO7AfX2xpcHxvw/Pb86fmUA9IP2uqwhmCPf38vlWphUld8fB96ygv0l/S9LEbVRS+wffch120nkvda6XqeIriMYKf/d4dKNjd2JltVmWhu8ll4yWuqlRn9QxwfNBltvqqbPFU5wdcJtllq5X8DFM+Gyf3nvIYAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-12-19 17:23:44","box":7},
{"id":20,"question":"bacitracin zinc","answer":"Haplopappus Cass.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJFSURBVDjLpZPNS1RhFMZ/5733zkzjR/ZBCUpoJdUiBCkll4m0CUKJIGpVSLjyL2gntDFop6shAolWbcSNIW0ircHBUHCloo3VjNY0jjP3831bWA5ai8Bnfc7vPOfhHDHGcBjZAENji7N1cSj7IcdqY2zkKoiC2qSFNsKPYoXpTPbBynj/4j8BlbLL9c4L3OqoZWLmM4/vXdpX9OJtHq0lBXQdBIgxhvtPZmZ7ui+yspZrjwKfWExxtMbh66YLAgj4geZnyd2YzmT7Vsb75/c5UEqwDLgVl55r57hxuYY3c18Y6mtDgO1KSBBETMwV0VpeA2f3ARKOwvUCcgWX9bzH0NhqvC4Okx9zBzNpPdGQ4OHIrJnOZLtWxvs/2AChNnhRiFIKy8j/ZjILiALYLgc4YnO8zsJSIWUv4Pt2CMBU+tteoxtC0YN8wUdEV1eItMHCIdSagru5l0kQaZ4OdqC1wQAWhqQNnudR3PGrANu2aGmE9FJATSxJwinhegHDr1ZRAmGk0ZHGAMYYMJB0dh0ogOVs6VNqcoGtosYv1+9lYikHERvBQsQCozBGCMIQ3w+rDtKjvQMAd4bfL59vFqYzQasjNoM36wi1vzvHgBFNwo4x8nKNreJOFfBHy9nSXGpyoSPSYOGgqZCae8TJ5BkERb68zsDVZygSlD3/b0B6tPf2byempRFO127T095JQ6wJFBTcJk7VhCRjYItUT/mgrgxOvWtrPtLdEG8gYdcT6gDRGjERWsosrS2TKwbMP78rcth3/gX/0SEvLZFG1QAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2024-04-12 03:20:29","box":7},
{"id":21,"question":"METHYLPREDNISOLONE","answer":"Juniperus virginiana L. var. silicicola (Small) Silba","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-11-06 21:12:24","box":3},
{"id":22,"question":"Isopropyl Alcohol","answer":"Setaria reverchonii (Vasey) Pilg. ssp. reverchonii","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKRSURBVDjLhVNLTBNRFD3TTju1FCcBaxuaQEr94ydiZIHGpcFISBOi0YREZWHCVoyRxKUxxq0LXcACQyLsjO6KjSEiDfHDz0S0CLSxlFKd2g7MTDudGd+bMAQCxJucuXfuu+fcO/PeYwzDALVoNMqRuI3guq7rR4g/SEBC/Svxc8T3EUTD4bCGTcZQAUI+RvxLr9d70u/3o6KiAm63G3Qtn89DFEUkk0lks9lRkrvW3t6e2lCgRZFI5F0ikaDtjN1MVVVjYmLCGBoa6qccC7Z1kQafz4f/WSAQAGlyaXOOpQ+SNNUymQxcLhc4joPD4TBzkiRBEASkUimEQiGzdlcBlmWRy+WgKIr5Xi6XUSgUUCwWzTVN+IAzeOOde71orP0eAaOkbrDWf6Cw2+3mBLSYgny3KULXPOUY2BUB/hMd4IOn8XfhMGYjvU+2TECLLRLDMNA0zYw5JYa6Ghke/hyEn9/gZEqo3OuHp7qW3yJgESjoNPSdlb8gWCOCr29BMT0Ip5tBYnIWqlL6o8irzVsEaHcKSqQCen4cweok+FAblNRz2JxlODx1cEkzGWmVbTl7Z/jHhgCF1Z3GYjIKf+U8+ANhQn4Gm6OMUiGI9MhHg5Gl1sbu8UnKNc8B7Ui3ipxEcwvlpVFw6hz2N1xGabkXdqeBYqEOmfefEZWac4e6xz9Z22hbn+BmLBZbi8fjEBdG4NF/QdUDSM88hQ4FawKJR6cxLDZl86qzZdtdoDYwMBAkQg/2LL/ovNLVh++Dd7G0OAau9hTkrKgnnE39GW3f/Z6enpUdBSx7ePu4eq+zi4VNw+TbV0gsxFd5b9X5i4+mpnY63tsErl6okhvrfWzT0SAMR3FMXsnean08Pb/b/fgHqpjCspi90kkAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-09-14 22:26:46","box":7},
{"id":23,"question":"Clindamycin, Benzoyl Peroxide","answer":"Plagiothecium denticulatum (Hedw.) Schimp.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-04-13 00:06:32","box":4},
{"id":24,"question":"Carvedilol","answer":"Cuscuta globulosa Benth.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAIhSURBVDjLY/j//z8DJZgsTV+9fAu+uHo8+GzvXECWAV+c3R//mTn9/ydLu4eka3ZyY/ts63T3k4Xt+4/GlqS74JONY+9Hc5tdH4wsmAmGgWv9xQKX2nMPnapOF4A1WzsEfjSzefLB0FwUHoi/szPX/05P/f0rOWk9ugHONWefzNl44X/B/L3/o7LXnn1h4fitN6i22Tx7W5tpxqYHxmnrChh+p6X+/rd10/+fsbF/f0REmiE0n7F3rDz5wb7s6Bu3gt3Vz80db69zTd1mlr11tUnGxt89Cw/8N0ha9YDhZ2LC+p8xMb9/hEdc+h4Ucu+br//JFXFNi5zKjz20KztiDzIMGFgzP+iZboQZbpSypsAgaeUjvfilqIEI9C9bf8rk3Wd8kz59sHV+BQysa8DA+vNe1+RreV94S96UiE9pff7/I1scPnlW6NWgBCLQvxKOVaeO2ZcfW2pbcogTGFgGwMD6+2/alP+rYhz+Na5O/L/lytT/F57t+t+/O+t/eL/uf/NsyR4G17oLBUD/Pgf69w3Qv6XILnqvbbT+nZre74RWlz8bL0/4v/HapP8g0LMn9X//nnSQAd8ZnKrPPJi85uJ/oH9f4opOn2rD/9uuzPmPDDZdmgoy4D+DQ8XxArvSww9sivYX4DLAMkf6e/eupP/tuxLAmtt3JiBcQEzqAypsCe7R+N+7KwVsM4gG8cFhQGwSBiruAOJPIGdD6Q6QOAAJO6JfeUJqowAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-03-24 06:06:12","box":4},
{"id":25,"question":"Atenolol","answer":"Bolbitis Schott","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKGSURBVDjLpZNPSFRhFMV/33vfzDjOvBmlRkuz0THKIjGN2qSrFkFEBUFBG1fhtkW7aB1UUNDCyIJaRC3aRAXWxkroHxpCRGaY2uS/GWfUGUfffPPe+1poUbvCs77n3HPvuVdorVkP5P8Ujz3ae0IVtj80w80U5l4i7MlO8a8OfvQmTsvAyXvBjR1EG1pZGHvD8PNbs/JCz7u+snKrdS5fCi3ZjuFp8NC4nsbTGldrmq234kx7p4hWtJEd/YxfKKzIJsoq4zEZq4zWdR3bHimWtCgLmH91FYDKvEKlM0QThyhOP8BfLpgYGsb1/Fwe25c0UjknoRxP3OubJjmnKBQ1ExmPZNYjOdaHSvUSbTyMPdWD8M3jC1tgz2Hu7WK5YvdWo1B0RcBnULs5wvPBFAtLJaojgpXxx5QvPCO67Sj2ZDeGr4TK1TP1YoiB6vPE6psAhFy2HQASm8IIDb0DKdo3DOLLvaaq/Qhq5hamX2Mvxpnp/8DgtmtsrGtE6FWeUbDd1TxNSNSEiWaeYWbfo9wapj9ex8OmkK0l2f+JgcQVahsaCf4RviysrCoJAU7JwTd9n13Hb/PlwTlG+l8T2NqCPZ9mvu0ivnAMQztIn/y9ZWO56KIBpRxms3lGvqVRn57Q0NJBKLSDyaFR9IFLNDXvoX6zRXYhj+c4aA1ogVwuOtr1tEhl8tTFLO58TXH1Zjf7dzbgj7fQfOou/sgWPDSy3I+ssphK51ipCIL2tCxkJ8eLyok3bQmKcNAQN54mMdZGEkKsOfUQvw4DSbzS8sZn8iqX/jEl1VJ64uDZ3sqAFQrJgCmkNDFMgWmAYQgMucpb00KAdh2lVhbnM+nR5Hex3m80WCd+AqUYHPPwkaN5AAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-04-22 12:30:58","box":3},
{"id":26,"question":"DOXEPIN HYDROCHLORIDE","answer":"Cyrtandra kealiae Wawra","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJZSURBVDjLhZJLSFRxFMZ/995xXpYzaRn0AsloEUlQLSwqS5ShhGjTwtpZ0Toogly0iB4uWrWIVkLgvsVEi4wKsUULIwQxLGyU8TE6vmbm3v+9/0cLnXA06ducA+c7P74DxzLGUKHB3sPALZQ6h5HHkBKM/Ib2PyH8V3Q8GF1vtyoAg713UOoRsWSMSBQsB4wCtwD+EsxlXEzQzZVnzysBg71hjHlDtDpFVQSWcuAug6XAF6B9cCIQr4FCHhYm3iHEZW689m0AlOohVp0CIDeu8BZa8d04bXctLnVbiGKchalWJocVSkF4ewpRfLKa4OPLo6CHiO90WJ5QlLyDWHIe6d/HBBfWEnxAeE9Rfh2B+El9o0NmSKGDphDK7yKadCjOgldqRwuJkd+JJRso5MGxIVTTTDHfiRBnUH47s2P91O13mB7pslHe6t2FOQjcLwSl24RriuR+9bE000I+28L0jz7iu4rI0nWUO8jitCS6DdxSKoRwG8BAUAJfiJE9bTlL6/HF2vMdWutOpRRaa8JefkbUttW3DD0WBH4BnCTa3xtCuiAFuEVQXqhQtePqseMnT7NZu/v73zfheTaOsbA0WMYJUVzJMDXaiFdwkZ4h8E4A9LydrNi+d3EftrdyCktaGLPM768JIBPi2otD641iYCBS7s8eqQdgfN4HwLUicR4OS+BA2RPamFMp9bcfm/UqZlLKTXdtApRNN5urgVVY+d3Xw8uyt0pg2zbZbJZsNott21sC/pVgEUgmEgkSicRG+OJ/AUqpdDqdblNK1Zd/YK0WtNafN/r/AJRSSvzM+v9SAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-05-13 17:51:36","box":3},
{"id":27,"question":"Mirtazapine","answer":"Solanum umbelliferum Eschsch. var. glabrescens Torr.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-12-01 20:54:36","box":3},
{"id":28,"question":"Gemfibrozil","answer":"Nama aretioides (Hook. & Arn.) Brand","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKKSURBVDjLjZJLaFNBFIa/ufcmJjHa1tYoiCIiPhCfoNKVoCIuFAWFLqS+QKXo1qUg4lLBhYIgNiiCBBRBxbe0Iqjgo7WgFsWmtmbRhlhNSczNnTnj4ta0xY0Dszhwzj/f+f9R1lq6u7u3jj65cF8XcuihLFvSvev5vzOsurq6VhhjXkhQmepiyF88zObLH/5r2vO89V4mk+ltbm4+Fvt4L51sBCwEQTCpUUSw1k6q4/F4KNLS0rLEGHNeUq24aIrPOv55yXEcRKRWK6VqgjWCaM+99LSUBQkbAE7dHEIELIQDAgKc3N00vkaNYGYrrtL8etpZExCBZXPjYwLhfd9fAsAYA4Db0NAwUldXN1h5eWOnU+yhku1n4a6jHG//QkxVGRj6hV/x+fS1QG64SMyt0tEzws3n3/lW0C8nEOzFVZqRJyHB73KFjesWs2NNkruvvnNiz9JJvlztzCPS1u5kMpneXC53LP/wCqW318BarLWU/YAfoxqAx2+GaoMVDUUf8j+rKCUTPdiHi2bkUceY8wrXQmCEs21rELFYwMWS8MD3fYql6ngKzus76ekpi5jQ8VjEoeIHnM704yjQRhAj44lYSEQmEezHQVO434FSCi0W32hcJwJYFCbMXyzWCloHVKt6AsGr2+lkSiBMh9FyQER5tG2bhpYq4IAFq4SYF+XM9QEKxdIEgu0HQoK7nbiuixGLSwThN+3vjtCUmIfCIV8e5NDaczjEKPtjHmitl6/+9KAvMSOOtZDNZvE8l/mzYVZylE0r11EfnQMO/KzMITVVk4iCpxTq758+sKhxw7xkdGOuFAxe/lzoWXXw1qUlC5pW1E+pJ+ZNR0uAEkFZg6gyvQN9DBcD/gCIAXUVRPlHKwAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2023-08-27 22:44:01","box":4},
{"id":29,"question":"Guaifenesin and Pseudoephedrine Hydrochloride","answer":"Liatris tenuis Shinners","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAEXSURBVDjLY/j//z8DJZiBLgZkz37Ynjrz4ReyDEideb89afrDf5ET7v4n2YCEqXf7qpY9/T9r76v/Xu03STMgasLteaVLHv+fufvl/6k7X/y3qrlCvAHBvTeXFC54ANbctv7p/95Nz/5rFZ0nzoCAzpuPsuc++D91x4v/jasf/y9aeP9/89rH/6VTTxJngGPDtc3xU+/879789H/5kgf/02fd+V+17OF/yZhjxBmgVXCaRT3v7BqP1mv/a1Y+/J824/b/woX3/osHHSAtECVjjqy0Lb/wP2/+3f+Zs+/8F3XfS3o0inntXWSeffJ/0tRb/0Ucdv4nKyEJW25ZYBh/5L+w5fb/ZCdlQYMNs4WMt/wfuMyEDwMA0Irn/pDRT58AAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAGGSURBVDjLxZO/alRBFMZ/c6MmomKhBLv4AIJiYekjCFopKSzyCnkGW99BbMTOQhsrBcFKsLCJhRYBNYYsWXNn5s6Z81nMGu+626XwFDOHge/PmfkmSOIk1XHCOvWn0ZdXsulPpAFZQbUgG5BlVDOURLWELEJJXLz3JMwTVOP0tfsLChIEmC2A4OD5g0UHebLLWQl5bAcBJAcC4i9D6FZRiUtGMMOHb9j0PXhGGtruA3hCnpBHzly+i5d+CUHNgCFPoDIDjcEJeQ8yNCxxYL/2m+U55Yh7mpFE8NhE7GiRwGsi7bzF8meoA8io6ZC1jfWm7AnVCPLld1DjPna4y/kbm4Djw1emH56h2oN6VFNzIKOOCI6DFCTKj48cvN6m9jtQC64yAjcXrjrnoBu/94VbDymTPSZvHs/A6RgsT0gZqC1M/46AJcJKx7mbW8RPL5m+e8HKpeusXbmNI1AFDHBkmZHzFpO9p3fkJSNLqEQsfgc6uhCQJRgy7qlF2ypXHynMEfy33/gbubc6XKsT2+MAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2022-11-17 21:49:27","box":5},
{"id":30,"question":"Naproxen","answer":"Viola lanaiensis Becker","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJKSURBVDjLdZJNSFRRFIC/82YazQJpkVgbQV9aU23cuQtatIxaREi4C9zmQvrBpEUGLtvnQkqIVi0jgmzjT5PWZJYwIiEG2iInnR/ffeeeFuNMjtaFwz1wz/fde+69Ymb03Z1Ine88uZxMSuP84lo4PtKb5x/j0rX7zafPtee2torlxWymY/rVWCRmBlAneZ/9Hk6M9tVJLl693dx5tiNXKBbLix9nOzJvnkUANQHAjTtPU+n248uYNc7MLIYvnwzkAS5cvtUcnjmVKxZK5a+fZzvm3z6PqkydAODKzceprs4TOfXx4Q/Tc2EUFelMd+UK26XSty+Z8NO7F9HeejEzBgcHHwD3qjIzo6WlJQGgqnjvWV9fVzPDzFBVCoXCw/Hx8eHkLjAUXn8k+y/NDNTAe8OXNLH221FSMODXWO8QMBwANDU1ScsRIZCDcKzGj7xjNe+IvZAQCADnnEAlx8xoTELrUSEZ/IXLkbK6GbEVeRIiJIIKEIigqtQEzjmcVsBjjYJIBf65HWOeXVgIEAIRAqMmSAJEUUTkgd2dU2LkywoIIkYAeKOSG3jZJ1BVnFaK1Hu2nKcpFeDUCAJQBcQQE6qPXieI45gdNcxDKTbUV/o8lDBiJ3VwNbz39S0UdgznoeSMWEHNUBNMKmf2tgfG6gUNDQ1svh5lZWWFkaUlBtracM6RTqdZmJuju7ubqakpenp6mJycJAzDWgtiZvT391trayuq+t/w3tdm7z3ZbJZMJiNJgI2NDRYWFmqL3nvM7EBe/crVvwPwB5ahnKoTKjg4AAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2024-08-23 00:30:44","box":3},
{"id":31,"question":"HYDROCORTISONE BUTYRATE","answer":"Melica subulata (Griseb.) Scribn.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAF7SURBVDjLpZI/S5thFMVPXt9aakBjIYJvyFycnZw7KDhkcCi41BK30tpkqA5d/QClLv0IKuIQB/8Mje5dVLCCxhQtkg+QFnLPuU8HqYY0Q4h3fLjnx+9ynlQIAY+ZqNfFxcr8ypvtVwN9A2icp/Fr53uq84SlajEv+ZyoacknRWVlwvhwDk6h1qh93lzY+dAV8L5anHL6cpLOFTJPR5F+kkYcxfDgoAt04rR+gtqvq9XK24NPABDfh78V85KWX2QmCmPpMfyx34iiCHRCLngIkAtGwoyD/3L3AFFzyVBSyA5lQRdMwtntOX426qAJyfMEpHB1U1vbLVU//gcgNT08mEHTmqCEox+H1zRubbyulABg9svLY5q+75Wr77q2IOPMyLMRDKRiXDYu0B4GADOum3Gxs4UHAxMoQsFRb9SxubBTal/cLx+udqu3DUAwEJKDLfb8E+M2RRgFQTDrA8CW7gxc/RnQCBPhoU8DaxF0wh9jsH+0d9cGewf8BRKi/IUanjYRAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2023-04-05 05:07:10","box":3},
{"id":32,"question":"sodium phosphate","answer":"Pseudocydonia C.K. Schneid.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-01-06 11:50:02","box":1},
{"id":33,"question":"DHEA (dehydroepiandrosterone) Pregnenolone, Progestertone, Testosterone","answer":"Juncus squarrosus L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAM+SURBVBgZBcHLT1xVAMDh333MkxmYAYZOwbGGPqRaHq0gpIBGba3GR2KibjQmsHDXsHDjP2DSmBgTU7swUUk0ajemK1HapjYIoYRqi4DoUAsNjwIyw9wZ7tzHOff4fZpSCgAAgJHJ4UHgPNADZAATKAG3VKAufTb49c8AAACaUgqAkclhExgF3nwtdyaSjmWw7BpsD4R0EGxxfXNMSCGvCiHf/vLlHyoAmlKKkcnhEHCju/HJ/hdzz2E5EVw8li2NsIqwawco4RHDZtOdYHZjdk744pnv3rpS0gGA0VMNx/oHmrspSA9f1xBCpyrC2IQpuBG2nRhrpRCPJp6mO/t4h+f63wMYxbMPBoCP3zn2qjEv99mkSjUQVJwEBTeE5UB+vUxpf59IehetLk9fYxvXF2dav7k1etfoHT756bnm3hOaEWNTF6CaOCgT3N4yqDo6i+sVgmiRyKG/cWvz7ARFzKLkRENOv72yVG8CPbnaFu7YG+xEdZ4wDhMgWN32cJwqdVmFVT/OcrAHriIlIuR3XM48dgrfFe0m0BA3a1i1N9h2bZLxVva8JMViQF3GoSltsyO7sNy7RFSZ8n+7FPbiJGJJfE+kTKWUpinwXAtFDjMkGZv20WIJNpcFuqqlOVMlWR7EWvdxmMX37oNSCCE0U4qgYHlWS4ORIhntZG3HxPFDhKMRok0x7v27izOTIhOeIROdJ+JZlJ0yY1O/IEVQMoUvfl8pPGg5Es9x7eEkqfgRwkYO37FRRopwIk2tO0FbdomnjvfxSP1RbixcYXp+AqNa8XTfExd/XLopDiUymPY6pd0p0mkXU7iENEVENzAr1+hq60Tqks6DZ5GaT1/7aXTPyepfvXJ53HP9n8YXb/JsSxd1Rg3pREBdWFIbdkiGXIqVLUJagtePnwfggxe+4HBTB0BIB/Bd/91f83fm/lz5i3NtPbSmTA7EFY1GmQbdplgusrAxxYWrQwBcGB/i3vYcgKMppQB46fPnk8IXl4Uvz77XP2QisygVR9M1Fv75ltXiFKc7BjiaPUn+4R9Mzf3G2v3SJ5pSCgAAgP6Pet+QQr4vZdAeyCANAJSMatnTveoBIAqUgUvTFzc+/B+ww5qo63KzbgAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2023-08-04 01:59:14","box":1},
{"id":34,"question":"DIDANOSINE","answer":"Silene acaulis (L.) Jacq. var. exscapa (All.) DC.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAMGSURBVDjLVZNLaFx1GMV//3vnzkymk5lEm/GRzWgVOkVcWRcRLK2YVHwg1geFQJfJIgWhmy7UQl24bcxQGjcqRHfiQikmiIKGKEWE1NqkQmjStNVOZ5J53Ll37v/porQkZ33OD77vcIRzjp0yV94bBTFmnRvBqIqVkbDFl+qksn/Lm1+eLx7644edfnEfYC6/VsYvTDkTTXild/PWBysUziqE9xiEGyRr1dBZOWtkuzr4am39AcAsHy3j7flYlN4et2mN6f6MlWs4tYV1D5F59CzdWzOkCy/jy4TuXx/MGRV/OPSOWveEEJ6x/kkxdGxci1X01jQ2XgRzG4hB1cGlUI2rdDZn6MoNspUz46anpwC8xu/H3xLkJm26i21/j7Mt4N5ZwhMgQuT2LxQOfIaJPXq1eXSQxygmNi+IUS8/PDbpP/F+TgRP4hjCWbvrqV4QoJsXSO5cZPDAOWSrQVT/lcLzn+RlmzHP3fg0b5Nr6M4i6UfO4KQPO5sRApFOkTS+wFlFas9heturuHQRIxnxsHK/9T1U4ytMvIkInsMZA9zjOOsAgUj5xP/9RtD/LKqzjcFHSyqe0RFYg3UC3bqMlzuINfZB2FqwBox2aJVgDTgDVktUDJ7VvRUnDU4MosKreH3PYHoaoyxGg5GgI40K+yjsO0747xIiO4CQEUmXFc9ptUQSIdJPITt/Ejz8ItY7TLIVI1sJSTOi195LoXKO8NYlZPMS6fzT6LBG0mVJbH8rRq1x32QPVvOdm+dxci/9+04h/Aw6uoufKeFI07w+T3NtjqDYT7F8gn+mT4cy5lhq4E27UP9azLp27VRQOEKv/hN3lycRYhjnBtBJEy3vgDEExSLZwRfQtWt0t5h95Tu34AEYSbW5eHYurfvJDU/QVzoCGYGxGwi/RVB8nNzwIYrlE/ixZnn68zkrqO4a042qKJuQKWOYGDp6Ou/6Slg/g9MGl4So5m2uzFTDXptZl6H6xkW3vgtwX6sfidGkxZhVjKiEShJBErEiE5aMZv71H93CTv//ct+662PTZOEAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-07-16 19:17:06","box":2},
{"id":35,"question":"Aesculus carnea, flos, allium sativum, Ambra grisea, Baryta carbonica, Ceratostigma willmottianum, flos, Conium maculatum, Graphites, Helianthus annuus, Juglans regia, flos, Kali phosphoricum, Larix decidua, flos, Mancinella, Pulsatilla, Viola odorata, Xanthoxylum fraxineum","answer":"Rhynchospora rugosa (Vahl) Gale ssp. lavarum (Gaudich.) T. Koyama","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAQAAAC1+jfqAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAABjSURBVCjPY/jPgB8y0FHBkb37/+/6v+X/+v8r/y/ei0XB3v+H4HDWfywKtgAl1v7/D8SH/k/ApmANUAICDv1vx6ZgMZIJ9dgUzEJyQxk2BRPWdf1vAeqt/F/yP3/dwIQk2QoAfUogHsamBmcAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-04-23 02:04:42","box":6},
{"id":36,"question":"Witch Hazel","answer":"Lecidea crisima Nyl.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAD7SURBVDjLY/z//z8DJYCJgULAgi6gUvvEWEOVY6aqJJsxw79/DAxIDrxw+9ee/blirnhdYKjHtcpKmd1YiZ+JQZKbmeHivV97+j0EGEGaGf4T4QIZPiYlXhZGsM2g4Pn/FyL+/x+I/Ec4DEA2vv32jwEetjAa6B2YYXgNeHD/Z9iOM19XP3j3h+Hbz/9ATRBbwbH19z9hL9zrkn0PpMIUCh4Jaqpz7IZF8/8/DAwMWKIcZzQ+mCD3/tu3v+8Z/sC88h8aDgRcgAzAfoa54C9WB+A3AORnmCYw/ZdEA/4hO/kvAwMDyS74j4j6//+w6ifkBYQmXAmJccBzIwCU7Hm5Y0odkQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAInSURBVDjLhZPda9NQHIbzVwlWryzthpWuIpWOieKYZXO2q1vC0KFr9aZM3Yr40QunspU2TVYmYhVRvNErwQtR3E0JTq3G2o80mc0Ql9dzTr/SYdnFA8k5yft78nLCjcxJNwKzsuoOiZoj2GKsi3NS1I7y4hIA7n9wgQvyz4KiWLphwNgyoRMq+jZ+MUyo1ToOR6Ra3wA6ua4b8F/2gL830WF8YRGB2VX4hBwOBEWrnxl3kGzQyXzyLJbfLuL+uwQevr+Jk7EsiBn2MmMBdbJ58UEEKx9vYfVDE89MBtTsTVjA53iiy/XbeD4XRaluwhWSNRZQIYmeay6cSsYxfCmFwfMpEGW4wjk4gxm4J7IECd6IhOW7z/AlkYRaawXQbyuTtCOJAQzPp/bU9gtrLOBHrUECJI3bP5bWypoJx7l9cE+tMO0TsTuIpl90uCq+xJnoEtP2hUV8Cp7G90orwMECGthQd5gynRxLPUWuoOOR8huPN//gyde/iMuvmLZvKgtlfBTFdsBgSNwslavQiOIACaCF0ofzRQv5bzsd6BrV9obSyI8EUCw34JwkAcd4aWFoWn5N00ihFi30+HwaM5LCmM4UGH5SLtX28uvMtlg2mwH2U9UuNHBlDUKu2ANdo9pDwjqqpNQSOwdyrSegXeih0Rh7wQ5da2lbdDI5RBqxT/Qa2ArdUK1ddLV7/gX7jb1QzdhGjVAl10262n0D7IXSSbtpa9vf+QeB6/JTIb6VuwAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2023-08-20 16:04:54","box":4},
{"id":37,"question":"ACETAMINOPHEN, CHLORPHENIRAMINE MALEATE, PHENYLEPHRINE HYDROCHLORIDE","answer":"Cuscuta globulosa Benth.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-04-21 22:07:11","box":2},
{"id":38,"question":"Triclosan","answer":"Cuscuta salina Engelm.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAI3SURBVDjLfZM7aFRBGIW/mXt3swmuaMjGBwqCBlQsRPCB2GknCIpgJSKKkNZGxM7CQrSw0Ngp2vsoLBS0srERUSMiKkFRYkLMO7t778x/LO7VxFdOMWc4//xn5j8wThL/wqnz9w6BrgIrhQNBuSzEQMp/odtnjm7t6m00cC5FQG4OK2rEkHHuyuP+/xpIdDV6GvRfvsWGvr5feuIdn96+4sLpfkxikReA9yl969exZecuEp/gkwreeyqJxwzMFjEwCQM6OmrUOpfAH1kJEU2k7x5sf1Fbunmzc/73sg4QDJ6/HmZUQ4UaiwQ+v/nKsb0QzEid/Ma1e25UnFuQtHPEh3eQwCdVfNJRBlBSpYaAEIyUoBaWdbSHB4hZAn4pztUJ0UAwMjT413gjQ4Og/eTRSMmdl2XErIpMWPMT+ew3zm4bofnsETePGDBUZmBYFsl2V5vgOkM0UpxqFppkc6Bslnx6ivrGY1Qbq1ixehnOuWIsqeCkzucnJ5KKz2KMmkzJPWlnL8s2nQQMJISxJP/I+8EHxDCLxRkUZpA1qfYe58uHMS7dvT8uOJySS4otbO4lipMoTqMwQbfGWd49CWGi1KdQnKVzTUqlNmwPrx1tAKS0kSxg+SgKk8XhMFHux1GYKpsLAylAez7QlExyRBS+l43ljb/MpuebrVWMGRYYKLPxMDfWlc9U61jdSxWwOqgHxTaQIV+w85HYakmZtecNWu2LH68f3IHYh6O+2N9AgHuaYbr9U/oB0sFcUlVzMrwAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-11-12 12:03:35","box":3},
{"id":39,"question":"tolterodine tartrate","answer":"Lipochaeta subcordata A. Gray","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-12-25 02:08:07","box":2},
{"id":40,"question":"Clorazepate dipotassium","answer":"Pedicularis sylvatica L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAI6SURBVDjLpZO9a5NRFMZ/b9Jq0iY20qoVxY/FELGgFoRuFQR18atLtUgHRyfR0Un/AKU4qVOxg6hLHXRwUhQaNUiLCK1iQSs1GvP9vvd933vvcUixCcnmhXMPHHh+POfA44gI//O6AGT5mejqb0QCRIeICREdINpHjA+hwmiFaA9CRd+5aacVYDTdB8bb6CLgwNoHCBQfnW934JdWiIsg1mtMHRCxgIOwTnAiG5HQ67CC1thgFV2dA+sjEjS6DcAqxCrEemwYOIsN3Q4A4wMasQokXBM1ixViXRCNBK0OIgC6VmhYlqBJ7GGth1gPVS9TXC1jwiqi6+0OrFGopVdo/zOYAERjVIXY7q1YXadWqJLYeYbySq7tBhEA4xXQlRUSmQkSBybpSR8DGyLGpV4s0zN4kk3bD1H6tkAQibQDHBHC/DzFF9cw7hKYECshWtUo512SAylMZZYt+y/i9vaz8OBEdwtABJJHJglLvyi9vIWVEERRWq3Qn74AKkd2eoZEysOL9KJVcKoFgFY40Qi9hy8hOkX1zSwhe5BohuRmF+t/BbGY2lv2jl5F+/7N7NRIct2BVhSf38ade4j9k8f78prCco7UroNYdx6xHsNjaWzwg1hskW1D4xntB1fW1m8PU+7u6OWBzOk7g/vimFoWkYD3Tz4xPJbBifZB/Djv7l/Pi7VHOwKyUyPfhyZmdkQjy4guNkLQdPdoPM3Pjx9YfHrjcVeniGo/iOXujXliBbG2qeRfx1pEZPAvfWh3mkWk9eIAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2023-09-10 17:54:52","box":2},
{"id":41,"question":"albuterol sulfate","answer":"Galium hallii Munz & I.M. Johnst.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-01-23 18:44:46","box":7},
{"id":42,"question":"Mesquite","answer":"Prunus cerasifera Ehrh.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-12-12 10:24:15","box":1},
{"id":43,"question":"BUPIVACAINE HYDROCHLORIDE and EPINEPHRINE BITARTRATE","answer":"Primula alcalina Cholewa & Douglass M. Hend.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-12-17 13:55:56","box":3},
{"id":44,"question":"Risperidone","answer":"Empetrum nigrum L. ssp. nigrum","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAHdSURBVDjLpZNraxpBFIb3a0ggISmmNISWXmOboKihxpgUNGWNSpvaS6RpKL3Ry//Mh1wgf6PElaCyzq67O09nVjdVlJbSDy8Lw77PmfecMwZg/I/GDw3DCo8HCkZl/RlgGA0e3Yfv7+DbAfLrW+SXOvLTG+SHV/gPbuMZRnsyIDL/OASziMxkkKkUQTJJsLaGn8/iHz6nd+8mQv87Ahg2H9Th/BxZqxEkEgSrq/iVCvLsDK9awtvfxb2zjD2ARID+lVVlbabTgWYTv1rFL5fBUtHbbeTJCb3EQ3ovCnRC6xAgzJtOE+ztheYIEkqbFaS3vY2zuIj77AmtYYDusPy8/zuvunJkDKXM7tYWTiyGWFjAqeQnAD6+7ueNx/FLpRGAru7mcoj5ebqzszil7DggeF/DX1nBN82rzPqrzbRayIsLhJqMPT2N83Sdy2GApwFqRN7jFPL0tF+10cDd3MTZ2AjNUkGCoyO6y9cRxfQowFUbpufr1ct4ZoHg+Dg067zduTmEbq4yi/UkYidDe+kaTcP4ObJIajksPd/eyx3c+N2rvPbMDPbUFPZSLKzcGjKPrbJaDsu+dQO3msfZzeGY2TCvKGYQhdSYeeJjUt21dIcjXQ7U7Kv599f4j/oF55W4g/2e3b8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-11-11 04:45:20","box":1},
{"id":45,"question":"metoprolol tartrate","answer":"Ptilimnium Raf.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAGWSURBVDjLpZG9S5thFMXPG2NUxE8oxFAtKFnyLwiCHaxOnToodmoVh0qJFBVcRXQLuOhWLLQoWtsIfkCzmNLioA52EYz64mBKFAJKCXnuuU8HWykaS3i92z3Dj/O717HW4j7juxm8+TZQMvS1f9QzgNRZUnuKBTj/KkSTfbGG8tBrVYWbdUEqKMzQcFuEGzRc+tD76aQgILrZNx6sCI01V7XAcQBahaoiJzlkf2WRzv5E6jT1mUamlvvXv99SIDVAEgqFKEESYgU+x4fyQBnCwTAiDyNPjZGRzlh7Y0GFgbXn08HKhlck4Z65ECFC1SE0PXiEUn8AqsRe6gcO3IPol+Fk7NYRZ7reDbrn7tvjjLs392zRed+97Bymj2KJncTJZe4SF/kL1FbXwhh5cucXxMhLMTL/d//4YjVq8rK0f7wPv68UdTX1kLx0FlT43zyebLUdbR2gKuKrcWxN7DoA4C/23yYvMBSoVYjhdV40QIxAlLCWECNeAAT1TwPx2ICWoCroTYFXCqqglwYUIr6wAlKh1Ov8N9v2/gMRLRuAAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAIwSURBVDjLlZLNS5RRFMafe9/3vjPOjI1jaKKEVH40tGgRBWEibfoPQoKkVdtoEQQF4T/QqkVtWrSTFrVsF1FgJbWpIAh1k2PNh+PrfL4f95zTQk0HHKkDD/cc7vP8uHCuEhF0q/KnmXNgGR248PZFN4/GISXMC8L89DBPV0Dp4/SsazJjrtfb9/vdxfn/BgjzY5M8Aq8nBya+V3h93vtnQHFxat4kszntJAAAxus1YvnZQV5V/jyTEZarwnwFLGeFZdT0ZFOJdD84qoCDOpQ7grZfRNj020JSEOKvwvxGiF+q0tL0N5PuO+Mk0nC0B0BDsYCCImyzAIktBBloMwKJLSgKYcMAcdhC2KpVlIig+H5qxcv0n0xmj4Gbq+BwC2wtJLbgHUlMEFJwUpMIGpto16u+kJzSACAk+WCzvNbe+AVljkOYIcQQou3TbvdOJo+g4aNdqzaF+PT43HJVA8DQpcVIiPPtaqlEUQzlDELsTpgYwgTAQIjQqlUCtpQfn1spdmxh+PJSQyw9CrbKgM7tvcISQAxlBhC3GuCYXk3cWP25m3M7dk88qbWBRDVApaATOSjPBdXXwYEP5QyCgvjE/kwHgInHtHYBnYA2owhrPiiuw0sOw3EZFEagIB7qChDiYaUcNIoFtP1KxCTPhWiDw7WbXk9vKpnOgsI4exjg6Mbq96YQPxm79uPOvqvbXx4O3KrF6w8osv2df17kr5YXJq7vnw/S0v3k7Ie7xtud/wAaRnP+Cw8iKQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2024-07-15 15:38:21","box":4},
{"id":46,"question":"ALCOHOL","answer":"Lactuca virosa L.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAK5SURBVDjLjZBbSNNxHMVXDz3UQ0892AVSs4Q0shQRA5uzCFGL5Rxqc1u5mZpNnWNN533eaDr976blZeFllc7mMLMl6IOGqdOpS4vAPaRbb6FiQjpPm5QahvmFw5cfP87nezgkAKS9JI4+zp5Wey3Ot57AnMZ9rYnn0RAV6HHoz/+eZl74SYq12d2x0OaGnapL9azeF6CBeYxY6PSHrZeDH8OVsOmCsaA9BYva8/u+AKroo5V2cy8Wh1RYMz/D8nsV5id60F/sZ90XgBoew51pydxYmuyAY7YTKxY97AMEihKu6v4J4JK92Ep26CLBIEPFoqwl033HCGHqT7uOj69dhbAbcjFY+wAXOOd7AgQ+R/4CMIPPUJTsMEd1PBk71SjjQV4nQYUiF/lSAbo+tqCkvwi+eec0F/lnD28BZPRLg0+Sb6Gz4B5m2sRo5dNAMCioTQpDk1kM9bgQVaYMlJsy0f6pAen6NAQlB6i2AAq6Z/uXfu2uwrTZZMjGH6HCJEDxaDpyRlMg+pACtoqFOVXU/wurKI6GYkKEfMN9pKvjwK26ibjSUFAl12B7GrENOHi5RqQQpe0qzIeWBW5dDArb2ei2KGG2GSF7lwK6zBcMoffrTfOB4OeJVL5peeAbUPpSh9xGLQSEBvUjqxAo5hFfcn29a7oaXTMEXCPt40DWl4TAVLdVknt4LY3G614xzDogmQE4I0DCABDTDdC1ADEEROT4ocdSj51jmFK6ACBNSfzXxzrk4L+yg9kLMPUbiNdugKZxIFINRModuPLwNB4b76LMyNo0l71lbSew1oTYOkoyEJs3DK4RYL9xJtADDANwx5WifA6xvCjclnqj0pi4edm1XW8nQEr63JwU1FNEzQ6ktej900dBzptyahpk8SRCsk3wvPHCKs9KLEgQehuchiVX7N+73NXfL+Zkqi9OGtlWAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJhSURBVDjLY/j//z8DPnzu3DmhkydPZh45cmTd/v37i3fu3Jm7efPmorVr1wqB5PFqPnv2rPCJEycuHz58OH7Pnj0pO3bsCN+0aVP8mjVrFi1duvTO/Pnz1XBqPnPmDM/x48dfHzt2zAVoSNeTJ096Hz16tPXp06exGzZsCJw7d+6M6dOnF2DVfPr0aSagxomHDh2qAzq/F6hp1uPHjzc9f/68EmjIbiA7C2i7V39//yasBhw9elQOqPnAunXrKm/dulUE1LAbaEgbyAVAl/Q8fPhwG9BbDu3t7SewGrBm636v9EkHXq9atSrowYMHa16+fJkLshmIpwP5m4CG1AIDt7yhoWEHVgMWr9sZ7NO098eyZctKgYphNrcDNYOc33H37t11nZ2d2ZWVlXVYDZi0aIu5c9WOn4sXL7bZu3cvKPCm379/f/OzZ88KgZq3b9u2TbuiouJWUVGRFFYDolo2K9uVbPk9Z86c88CQdl+9enXPrl274oFh0jdt2jSf8vLy14WFhbZY00Fu20Ip66LNZ/JmXfxvl7/6tU328mcW6UueGCYtuumaPuVWaWnpzIKCAg+YehTNXb0TWhrben44FK56H9974r9z3uKspPLJtSml3XOj8zpb/dI6vPLz83WQ9cAZ7V29LUC//T948OD/grK6fzbp8ychKywuLubIy8tjQncxmGhp72rZsmXL//fv3//fuHHj/6y8khOZmZmchPIJ2IDW1lbJ7u7u/x8+fPgPTKL/07MLT6SlpRGlGe6CnOLaFcDQ/p+SkXciJSWFaM0oYZCclumbmJjITopmEAYAfvG+1+IMmV0AAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2022-09-20 04:10:41","box":7},
{"id":47,"question":"Lidocaine Hydrochloride","answer":"Yucca gloriosa L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-11-21 22:08:10","box":1},
{"id":48,"question":"SALICYLIC ACID","answer":"Sanvitalia Lam.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAGGSURBVDjLpZM7a1VREIW/fXKTIhAfVSQIIY2PWkEELe0FiZVgWkvBVhCsrLUQ/AdpxCKIhelstRCiAcFExEbRhAu5j71nLYtzvSeHXF9kYLOb2d+etWYm2eYw0QFYefTmNrAIXALOgY1JyFRVokogCQU70x1/OH3yyHlk7lw7k7DNzYevn/g/48Hqhm3XFQCXAW6sXscIy4SEJCKCCBEKIgJJvLi1zvtPO4OxBOQTAMM8ZH7h2B81b25sA9Dr55kxwPYsQM6Zz9tfsY0MViC51m/j0Q3giNQA5A7A05W1f3ZfIfYDEsDyvZf0JWRYu3+Fj192Jz5eWjiKFQBUNaCmfetlLpyd53uvjJPnZmda51e4tAC1rm4/yDZ7g9L6MYfJ0R44qTSANKpgMMj0chD9/FcPXIb7PKChT5rs6al0EODSAFRkIAE8f7XVSuzuDSdXMOpnByCkLWDp7eOrB9z+rQT7RzOJoWfLd9dP2b6IdFwqYGEFVgEHlqg31wZ1oXoHkA67zj8BVEcprN9nEQAAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-07-04 12:20:23","box":7},
{"id":49,"question":"simvastatin","answer":"Campylopus tallulensis Sull. & Lesq.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-11-12 01:03:58","box":2},
{"id":50,"question":"Mepivacaine Hydrochloride and Levonordefrin","answer":"Aconitum L.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKZSURBVBgZpcFfaJV1HMfx9+/Zc9QtO0unOMdasEibGf65SLOCJWRX4p0gCCVddBVYF0FEF4Hsom668jIN6iJJvYgoRoOMeTBdEoORf2rqJseca8ftHM+e5/f8ft9P5+JcSJA3vV5OEv9HwiPc+/HlqbnRPeIRnCRq469KJiTtwjQo0+uS3lzVtx9JNG+eRaZvZfa9TBWLVpGpa+Dgb85JYuHnYa3s20+oTZGsXE/6xDZW9e6FjtWAoaJGdrdCNncZv3CVzv5h7k+e5KlDky6lRaZyVh1dWrP7c5ChWKdYvEBafhHnUvzc15S6trJi82FQZP7iJ1i0fbQktPQMn6tb8QBkFPOnKea/w7JbIAOE5X+RV7+ief0jkJEvTCOzCVpS2mQCDEUPVoAzbLmC6yhQzFDMUMhBkaRUJjSXNgK1lDZFAwnMo1jgkggsgytwyjl2tUotzzm+SViMWDSjJaFNJpCh6JE8kgcyoInIyUJB/7ohDp86AuZQtBItKW2KhllO0vk0sTHJBxcvgcbwFvAhsHHNMwz17qKePeDt2xf4tNR5n5aUNpl9tvT7F0e7h45g+W2CeV577g2ijGgRQ1QXZ3m+/yUafpm3Zs5NZ8eSFSltfQcm3p39ZsdR19FFefNBsnCaKOPW39cpLBCsoIgFS3md7U++QqNopr/cGM9SHqJo6xvTP9xLSt1kISPEwIbyAMEiUcadxRnWru7l8ux5zv85fsUHdjpJPOzGl1u3JKXy1Hu1u2SFx5snC57Bni3sHtzHxEyFsWujkz7wQnVEuZPEv/1x4tkNivZOkj724eObhpm/dGb6UH22Z8fA3u6fro396o091RF5Wpwk/suV44Nrow8fmw/vH2jcmYnWsW7ZYmluRIG2fwAIBqNZGcz/tQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-04-01 09:34:45","box":2},
{"id":51,"question":"Cetraria islandica subsp. islandica","answer":"Pleuropogon californicus (Nees) Benth. ex Vasey var. davyi (L.D. Benson) But","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-02-13 04:57:18","box":7},
{"id":52,"question":"Benzocaine","answer":"Lotus plebeius (Brandegee) Barneby","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-03-24 04:09:58","box":3},
{"id":53,"question":"Cladosporium herbarum","answer":"Saxifraga hieraciifolia Waldst. & Kit. ex Willd. var. hieraciifolia","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-09-03 03:19:01","box":2},
{"id":54,"question":"Avobenzone, Octinoxate, Oxybenzone","answer":"Ribes sericeum Eastw.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAFySURBVDjLpZM9a1RhEIWf7C6mWASLSEBsbUWb/AdrW8HKRrC3EgWttbCzUgQRtRK0ERVEm/Q2aiPoBtJEosZ7Z+Yci3tvdosgKxkY5m3eZ77OrNjmMDYBePhu55rNpbJOSqIEKVElSiZLC15UmpI2b104tTEBkH3l/MbRtf/JfP3x59P7FZS0BjB9dhlsqAQVRHTvtoFooQmI4NfV10TU6gJgmIPhxHFQdu7sIQ1EA9nCxxkAkTWfQZV6wAp83warq0TqKqkhAuvrALQ9ANvcfTnzz72wbd9/M/tnfPLhm7d/7Pni7U3bZgQQJbTkOpswu7+DNroKRkMLy6qhyaINkak5IEpYSwJC/bgXASmWVWT0maerkzkgpaUFNACGzU0AMhMDD95uMR51UTb3Xs2IKu68+Eobxc2nXzgy7j6ORwu3ENW1cO7sMbIG7Xv/Fg4yqZtaLyS/v/Ho05m2NI0sIotKESWy8kDAzu6f5wArhz3nv90eObvZ0Hw1AAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2024-04-14 13:02:59","box":6},
{"id":55,"question":"Diphenhydramine HCl","answer":"Helianthus strumosus L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-07-23 17:54:53","box":6},
{"id":56,"question":"Acetaminophen, Dextromethorphan HBr, Phenylephrine HCl","answer":"Salix calcicola Fernald & Wiegand","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJRSURBVDjLhVNNaBNREP7eZvNHU9aqBDxkiScvIh78Aw8qleTgz0lvHjwoivW/YBBBDxY8iIeiBiMoeBPBQIUqXnrQgxBy0l6aEkIWbDA0JTZtNrub3XVmQ7YEbRx4O+/tvPm+mXkzwnVdDJNsNuu2Wi1kMhnxL7uE/4jjOCgUCpvaZf7kcrknFMlRIcQOOm6nFaS955xMJiHL8nAA0zRvp9NphMNh/7Jt295ikEAg4DtoVyYvoGN8VF8/W/IB+JKiKDjwfgxR2YHucLouRkMW3hz65YNql2/dG5HsqfV2p0jH/X4N+AKziYCLO0cEHo67mBqn/4qMVdPB8ZYF7dLNi9A7M+bvNmKys09LnZnwASRJgmVZEJKLEIFIxB6gxYCkcHDdRHB55SXanZPWavsGpQDaX/NT4Ag4DUGp3v9KPpSB4Cxoua6NmWQc52pNytV8pM6+FdrhE9MEsssH4CIxwLs9857uF4+1ElAgEZosS+g213uVbHcAw9jogz7A7Eoec/onlEol77xt+hW40VLaMmTbYse72t5j12MjFKpuLPwVQWr0VI95Zy+C+tXzGCN7aWsMWxZ/TlDYX4LC+QGTCtMxng68AjuUy2VPVyoVj1nTNC/MYiIOtfA5S6xnw0S5pjWKau3784EI2IG7rq85/0QigT4Bi7r47YEW312DaX0YmAV+Rmau1WoIhUKo1+uIRCJoNBoeINv7otbnX6jNhaWBVqa+X9N1PcbMLKx5Flhzf9A0ukNnoVqtPs7n86cNehohNqaW991uF9FodG4zgD87aSjZlUUofQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2023-08-02 21:43:27","box":2},
{"id":57,"question":"riociguat","answer":"Abutilon incanum (Link) Sweet","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-08-12 18:54:28","box":7},
{"id":58,"question":"Octinoxate, Octisalate, Oxybenzone","answer":"Bruchia Schwägr.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAEXSURBVDjLY/j//z8DJZhhmBpg2POQn2wDDDof8HvOe3osYtXzDzCxuM2vP3gvfn4MJIfXAP22e0Ies58eK9r2+r//3Kf3YOIhq17eK9v95j9ITrv2jhBWA/Ra7kVEr375vXDrq/9+s57eUy+4IY0kJx2w6Nk9kFzE0uffgXIRKAboNtxlC1/+/GPljjdABc9+q+ZcM0Z3qmb5LWOQXOmml/8DZz7+qJB0hQ3FBerFNyNC5z/9nrXqxX+Pvgf35OMuSSPJSXtPfXQPJBc089F3oFwE1jBQTLkiZNtw51jq4qf/XVvuwsPAa9Kjexkrnv8HyclFXxTCGwsyERf4LctvHvPuvAePBf8pDz/Y1N45BpIbKUmZFAwAR3nW32nUrY0AAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-09-22 05:37:43","box":2},
{"id":59,"question":"Furosemide","answer":"Allophyllum gilioides (Benth.) A.D. Grant & V.E. Grant ssp. gilioides","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJ6SURBVDjLjZNdSJNhGIa/VSQdRQcSISQeBI4R5ZrZNIO2Mj3I6CCCfinRfoR2IoJM020sp8OcoHNQassG1laNpAgdhqI2f0GoOSwTS4u22p+b29zP3ft9Wi2b1gf3yftyX8/9PM/7UQCo9fTJeERNhBWpV9//lzkc+MAoHuTfZt84gvZWhDw95DjKQGb0grvrAmLNgS91CH7T/qwO+pvR8mFu4r9aD8BEps3+uZsIfG0kMi1DDAJEww5Ma7gMZE0AHZk2M5qXMJCQ24SFKSV803mIBHoxpdqLtRP435IENb8hDEgKj+UYXOMHSHtPYClnxzVvoGdg6xcRQxXcE9nwvTuP0o4sFLalwTnGQ8gph6WSja5bPOvf+352FLaBUiw5DKQan5iPk+qFuNHOhaTzDE5rUjEp4aBbkf7mjyHS5mjYTfrsxuKcGCJdNkQPMnDtPg8FLXtQ/vQUHo00oER/Ajn126PZym0sBhD70oI2PRas+XAOcVDcngHjuBqPxxoZY8eICipTCbSva3FVl4P06oTQbhmLtVLZRSIb4bUK4TCnwjt5GAWkX9p8u0uEmpfFkL8oQlXnJUifX4GmT4Zz9w5iVyUVpAGeJWc3GRYfjoFULL7Ph/+jHGfvsPFwWAWduQ7awVq0DigI5Dqa+6Qo0uUipYKaTCqjtizv3DsIt0VIBpYL36wUZkWa62RzSjSvISkirE+MZCm3Ri60ZULdW4XL7TlIrqAmdpRRCcwMZg2CMb+9H4uzlfB/bsNQLdfZpcpsWL1ejoxlv6gVIllMjRLz5l//wnDLIfGEev/8qGqffUTJ/d7XlFUd73GRyPad4o1ILKM2xZ7/AGAf1Jkquq5mAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2022-09-18 13:02:12","box":1},
{"id":60,"question":"Fentanyl","answer":"Ocotea Aubl.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-05-07 08:36:40","box":1},
{"id":61,"question":"Lidocaine Hydrochloride","answer":"Amorpha herbacea Walter var. crenulata (Rydb.) Isely","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAL2SURBVDjLVdNNaBx1GMfx78zO7Lu765qQWIPteqiH+IKCjTmkClIVPHi0pVDSXBT0sGhLUOvJl0OL4AuVBC+CLXpoD1KqweBBWFFajOChSTU20q2h6e66nX2Znfm/ejCJ8Qff6+fy8DjWWgCmz9f3AR/cV0pPhtIQSoM0hoEyAdAFmoAG2kAL+Bz41mNzRqmJh0fzk689MczO9YUphsIU25EeExK6sebPZo9v/ugfAKo7gZFC0gGgflvjOw6eAwkPUr7LvSmXhOviJ+CRsQy7irnyp5fW33e3AC1loWQilIGucAgkdDoRQQRBBK0B3OppAF4/e53JSo4HhvzhbSAfBiP7v5pHHZ2mH2kqJ2cZ+uxjwqBPNzb0IstAgAEc3eGna22WrgfrLoA4Ol2eXfrimZw3QDoeYWyRePh0GZ0/RdTu0o8NfWnAwkYn5sPF1Y4WYtoVR44cNGH01+iwXzT1FvVj76CApUNVxI2ApNNn77EZUrXviZSDsaB9jRKicv7lxxZdM4jm433jabO0Asdn6eTLOC7oQpnfX3gFfrmKnBjnnrmTuFJiLag4RotYA7gmHLyY+LoWmcounBNvYm81cLEkgyaVuXdRe+7GuVijPlPFSfpIren1Q6WE6AC42YsXvjy9e//EtdXbyHyKyqszYOH+946TKHiEbcOVuXMEUwfI+NDqxahYbCy89awFcAEWhvaKj6YO48WQaDTAcXGbDcIA1k6cQuaKYCHruTTaA7SI17eu501Vzw4Bbz84OU6veobvlgW5rubHTy6Q9i2+B8nEvxWysFoPUUJsbANaiKeA535eXqM98OjFFqktsXQQyqC0wVhLuVjkpadHudkK0UI0/gOkfPT5Jx/KvHH48f/9gLYgtUUowMLphXWyPnR7IVrK1k5g7WYz4MziMqV8hlIhTSmXophLcUc2SSrpkvJcDk2NkPKg8XcXLeWNbcAoda52eWWsdnllN3DXZnduVkwnfT+d9inkMpQKWX69Wv8N+GEL+AdfSH+n2ppttwAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAH9SURBVDjLpZM9aFRREIW/ue9FF2IULDQuaYIGtTBRWGFJAgqSUsEmjZVgo4mFWBiwVVjBHwjGwsbCShExIAghoEUMARGNGFJYhIC7isXGRbORvJ0Zi/dWY5fFCwOnuHz3nDsz4u78z5HTlx6NDB4v3KjWvd0dMMPNUFPcHHPDVTF3XBU1Y/uWZHVxsXzl6e3hibgwUBhvy7WH3bmWHm5fres4MBHXEw/16s+Wra8lHgBiV+f6mX0tA86VlkkBbgCsNxQH3Bw1MBwzR83Qhqflxro63Z0dqGkKIOuCBEHc8SC4OGJCCIJIQESRyIksEDfS+9bIAE1SAFwEBCIHEzBzIocgEbGAiqMhdWxqWQTL5kAE3P8BiYCrYwIuQBAii1JAM0JTpAxJxQaQxUJsxvTbSV7NP6e2ukLSSFjT/cBJ4kaS/HEggLsjIvgG0Is3T3hfnuLYwFG6dvbwcuEZcx+nKY7mbwbPskSAZC4k00GEIMLk64ccPtCHBqVvzxAqCcVD/QAjwcz+Rsg+M4gQbahv37/QJts4dfAiAJdP3Gfvrl6AXFxeWn58/k4ybKqYGqqKmaFJgplh7lRrKyxUZpmvzDA29IDS1Fly0VaAX7KZbSyO5q91de+42t87SE/nET59fcfshxk+L9VuyWbXuTiaLwEXgA7gB3Bv7m5l7Dd8kw6XoJxL0wAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2024-03-15 19:29:13","box":4},
{"id":62,"question":"Ketotifen Fumarate","answer":"Consolea corallicola Small","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAQAAAC1+jfqAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAB8SURBVCjPY/zPgB8wMVCqgAVElP//x/AHDH+D4S8w/sWwl5GBgfE/MSYwMORk/54C0w2FOcemgmSIMyH1P7LNCHiLBDcEZ/+agqwXaFbOIxLc4P0f1e7fUPiZGDcw/AdD02z9/5r/Vf7L/Zf8L/Kf/z/3f/ZsiAwjxbEJAKUIVgAswNGVAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAALWSURBVBgZBcHLi1V1AADg73fuuXMd5947jzuO+WgSylIhdROEJNFIkBptclmEuza1yPBfyHWLKBcJLdq0KFBMEotKxCBSNDVJ0xzHxzyqM/ec+z739H3hwKH95xozjblSqQQAAgCAIAACBvnQ8uLy93FjpjH3+ccnhCgYDPsACIJCIYBWP0VQFJFiWCjkPjx6ZC4ulUpyA6H/pezsJZPnWpaOzhqrVd28ecGN7LgHS4lare7xSqIUl61mHe8cKJTjkgggSVYk20espqnWmevS9KE0TYXuJd12U7vV1Gun2u3UoJMJYYggDoDx8XUUfWvfn+Kj31TenDazYaPR/m3twVa1iZqRUiQuj0hbHSF0EURAkCSJNG36bya3OjnQ/uoW+VDR+lm/m2o1M/1uS7eT6XVbQihADDA+PkPRNzFel7y7w+SnKwYvb1CZ7prtrShXn7S2UlIeKWu2elglEBFAp9OVpS3JaqI5lvv3WTpf/KXIO6LeaZ12qtfNdLLUsJcJIIgDYHR0QrWeGa/XQfmtLUY/OC/On7KxcU1ntG1T9YrKyJJe+65S9LaAOACaSSZNu8j8uvDIvX5k/TO5507ctHAw83j+M1fvzUvbbb120ws7KgJiIQioTzxhddB1udVyt1c2NTnl0b5g3+mBk38OtWvL5vbutXlqqx+ufeOn37+WDesiKIrCL/N3nLp13f1/VnQ6HWmaSbtdF7cVbjx6YPe2XfIot2vDq/LQ9+LzeywP74oCWoPMUt5XGakaGx23pjKmuqZqy3xi8/0FS9mKcqh6Y/t74Mi+456e2akwFBGEEKmpq4aaSj5qbahaf2PRxoW2O3t2Sporrj244NjZw+DYd4fdXrwiEokHg1ye5zZN7bapQQBB2IpXmA7B/seJi1dO2bPzJSevfmIkxM5f/tGUWeH1Qwe/XTcz/VqpHCMIgAAAeDj8w/Lwb0MDkVjDrGhx8sz/ABdNCpr3mlcAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-08-24 16:59:23","box":1},
{"id":63,"question":"Homosalate, Octocrylene, Ethylhexyl Methoxycinnamate, Ethylhexyl Salicylate, Titanium Dioxide","answer":"Acorus americanus (Raf.) Raf.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKdSURBVDjLbZNNTFxVFMd/781jICiCCFoSC5YgGGAQG/E7EhckJFqMe5suNI27Ji7r3qXbLk2rSRuFhU1asESgxvoRm5qQoIAikECMdcIMAzO8++6957h4MyjKSW5OcnPv7/z/554bqCoTFz4eUNXPFQooLymKKqBKmvRwibdYs7t++8oH3QAR6YHzCk/l+juD+3/tolq7BClMUIHibpkDo4hGp6hGCoBXc/0ng9eGTtLZkUNTAqKSVpW0entLI40NES+/+R5HAKg+nBvoYvrubxQKFVQEAKmpUEVFKZYqxCbh31G1QBBlI54c7KLnsVa8B1VBRPFe8SI4UQ5iy2eTC8cBFO+FzfslsmEdcRxjTYKTdN+RIarL0vZAPaJ6DAAQLzhvMcbw1nM9qfxUHarK5flfeOJgkovPrjJZKfxfgfWCtw7nQz5d+BljHc4r3gmOgCE3zzODJZr73+fEIx9x78Pe8dMXV2cOAc4JibUkAhrWE9TVQahIIPTG84z1rNLcN0Z5c5rWR/vIdJqp6Qvd79aaiHUeFzuM9TgvWC/VrHSGv9KSex1fWaKh7XFiv0XH6HCjKxcu/aPAC9ZYjPWpHa8kVcifrhVb2CDM5AnCMtmH8hBX2P/DZI5YsEkKcKIkTmhz64w/+CVNTYq4bUIpQtiE2oTlayvx0krpfFQbmMR5nHEYK1gR+twPjETf8PQrY2hyi8DvsXjzgKRQJBDL1kbp7bNX16cOe+C94hOfWhDhheafGB49Q5K/RBQ1sziXMLv3Bl9vRuTX7mzdu/3t1JFnJAwZeX4IDQK8V7JkCTLbZOrbWby1z1flCXbaX8Ss3aVYcXP/nYPZmRvfv5P+vOr8n7CY/B1KO4ZPlvtZtQHKd6Bc//3HL87VAH8DX5rXmGdCnY8AAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-04-07 08:37:11","box":1},
{"id":64,"question":"Red Oak","answer":"Pilea peploides (Gaudich.) Hook. & Arn.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-11-18 20:54:00","box":4},
{"id":65,"question":"Acetaminophen and DIPHENHYDRAMINE HYDROCHLORIDE","answer":"Quercus pacifica Nixon & C.H. Mull.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKUSURBVBgZBcG/b5R1HADg5717764trfQoVUpasAfU+CtRgmERXEwcHFmMgwwmjo7+BUyOxsXVmGidDHGQEAc1NsEQxQsm4g9sKYWgUErLXe967/f78XmKc+fOPR8RFzE3Pz8/3u/3Tey/SgA5iAiQM6MR25vxz/IXv3agjIj30Ol0Onq9nkajYaZNQBCJrAA7jyHUG8UiQImzCwsLTp486cyZM9rtKRARIAQB1OtN+y5ssI/PP7h+w+Ejr5UR0Z6cnHTp0iV/3vxQTkAEEEEOYKfHO9UByye+Utv8d2mXqRJFrVYzOzvr1DOnKbLIIYSQRQ4RCaS05+tr90GzUdhlpoSIUBSFejkFUvTMHz2tXraUZcvNG5cNhzsiEhHiv3uM1UAJEWE0Gtl6+Lux8WOOP3vWrZvfG/QfaLbGPX38Tdd/WVavZwe3C998vN9wmP74jM0yIqSUpJTAk4cW9Xv3HZ4/pT3Tsbc3cHvtO0c7r1hf/VHkMGVMbXyw9P6uqEWEnLPhcAim2ws2bl1RL1uurnyk37vr3sbPJiZnpVTJgFqzgJka5JyNRiOQo5KrgZwro+FA5EqVBlK1JyKT2YkBgDIi5JxVVQUeb99x4OAxE/tmPPfyW1qtKYsnXvfwwV+yrIyeU8UF8Wi41XR4s4Scs6qqwOrf33rhpbdd++kTT+w/IvJIrRy3cfsHjWZbDqZqT9mZuD891s9RRoSUkpyzKg3AnfUrFpfeECkZVbt+635JnTInABpNmCkhIkSENBrIaWh9bcXa6oooiKBoAFFkge3dW+zCISXA3NycZmubIiOEIJIoQkQGOSWPJgZefXHl0263ez4rpsuIuLy6uvouPB7elREZAeQAoEBwsdvtnoea2Pof+BV374GHrjgAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAK7SURBVDjLbZJRSFNhGIaPTS3BG+8CA7ObwrDoqosKa2ZBIRQUBgVRSRRWloGalSYtC+HUMqlES7KZm83NpmvOZq6jU1qGpGiBNIgiMiON1NQOPv1noqXrwMt/87/P/3wfRwKkefFVrhSRUSq6eHFXpaVUxWPsorlYpsGwcuH9heUsURznlRV6GqHXNXO+NENbGdjPj2PLzgoF+Cojab/vossCb+pBKQe3jHgVGi+D4yI4DdBaAg2XoOqIi/IDkX8BSoWR16KsATxGVRT1Qjdq7qXHWVGYMvQ8PKpSL2Dm01C6W54BeO8m4r2t4q8VZVnFcSWOhsJooWsQuh2YMzt4dNxA5aFoKvbHcWePSl0u3NiuIusTJFpKjPiqhF6ppqun/kIs9twATdfAmg2Pz4gzB8rTApTuiuXmDr2AiDHSoXiDLAndd/gtM7PZ86KE7mWcRb1Ct5p7B5MoS0sSutVUn+jFuC2H61uWcHXjb2rFGIXr+iShO4lfbNkmXjNnLupXGk+99ToaOjs7f/h8PhRFwev10tFk+9LqeiJTtD5MFIepPQsFq0ckoTtJxwOoztC2G+nv9LVPTU3xv7hcT5+Rv1ZH4ZqR4GiXEn5KYrsD1OUhdMeFboRfaZnQLhvqA/PywVZC677l0x59+LR352I1kBGvAfqkhX9WW1sbswBlYDQYxy2ZnuxN/HLKTPc3MWbO4lVGotqcHH4yBKDNOwu47/sWjHPvCsZFmZJUyImBoniGijfj3qoLhAA8Hk8QMDg4OBdPcgTTr238+w0XLEUbJwTgdruDgKGhIbq7u4N5nraM0XtHxNaXMpEt8V3kwzEd7hTdpxCA0+kcXrj9gLkY/9FVfM6J5+u5CN6nh9GSGq42pejyQgAOh8Nkt9sHrVYrFouFmpoaTCYTjvzDk67UmDFNW7z8UStr9/8Aj3HtMz4GxWkAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-09-25 19:34:51","box":3},
{"id":66,"question":"Sardine","answer":"Capsicum L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-07-23 19:41:11","box":7},
{"id":67,"question":"Citalopram Hydrobromide","answer":"Anagallis pumila Sw.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-08-07 08:44:37","box":1},
{"id":68,"question":"Amoxicillin and Clavulanate Potassium","answer":"Trillium pusillum Michx.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-05-16 08:21:11","box":6},
{"id":69,"question":"Antimony Pentasulfide and Potassium Iodide and Polygala Senega Root","answer":"Ptychosperma Labill.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-04-13 16:14:11","box":6},
{"id":70,"question":"Oxymorphone Hydrochloride","answer":"Microseris sylvatica (Benth.) Sch. Bip.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-12-04 00:04:30","box":3},
{"id":71,"question":"Ammonium carbonicum, Apis mellifica, Chamomilla, Rhus toxicodendron, Urtica urens","answer":"Borzicactus Riccob.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-12-19 07:57:16","box":4},
{"id":72,"question":"Ensulizole","answer":"Porophyllum ruderale (Jacq.) Cass. ssp. ruderale","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAIwSURBVDjLlZLNS5RRFMafe9/3vjPOjI1jaKKEVH40tGgRBWEibfoPQoKkVdtoEQQF4T/QqkVtWrSTFrVsF1FgJbWpIAh1k2PNh+PrfL4f95zTQk0HHKkDD/cc7vP8uHCuEhF0q/KnmXNgGR248PZFN4/GISXMC8L89DBPV0Dp4/SsazJjrtfb9/vdxfn/BgjzY5M8Aq8nBya+V3h93vtnQHFxat4kszntJAAAxus1YvnZQV5V/jyTEZarwnwFLGeFZdT0ZFOJdD84qoCDOpQ7grZfRNj020JSEOKvwvxGiF+q0tL0N5PuO+Mk0nC0B0BDsYCCImyzAIktBBloMwKJLSgKYcMAcdhC2KpVlIig+H5qxcv0n0xmj4Gbq+BwC2wtJLbgHUlMEFJwUpMIGpto16u+kJzSACAk+WCzvNbe+AVljkOYIcQQou3TbvdOJo+g4aNdqzaF+PT43HJVA8DQpcVIiPPtaqlEUQzlDELsTpgYwgTAQIjQqlUCtpQfn1spdmxh+PJSQyw9CrbKgM7tvcISQAxlBhC3GuCYXk3cWP25m3M7dk88qbWBRDVApaATOSjPBdXXwYEP5QyCgvjE/kwHgInHtHYBnYA2owhrPiiuw0sOw3EZFEagIB7qChDiYaUcNIoFtP1KxCTPhWiDw7WbXk9vKpnOgsI4exjg6Mbq96YQPxm79uPOvqvbXx4O3KrF6w8osv2df17kr5YXJq7vnw/S0v3k7Ie7xtud/wAaRnP+Cw8iKQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2023-06-23 04:01:00","box":7},
{"id":73,"question":"Benzocaine","answer":"Arabis modesta Rollins","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAGGSURBVDjLxZO/alRBFMZ/c6MmomKhBLv4AIJiYekjCFopKSzyCnkGW99BbMTOQhsrBcFKsLCJhRYBNYYsWXNn5s6Z81nMGu+626XwFDOHge/PmfkmSOIk1XHCOvWn0ZdXsulPpAFZQbUgG5BlVDOURLWELEJJXLz3JMwTVOP0tfsLChIEmC2A4OD5g0UHebLLWQl5bAcBJAcC4i9D6FZRiUtGMMOHb9j0PXhGGtruA3hCnpBHzly+i5d+CUHNgCFPoDIDjcEJeQ8yNCxxYL/2m+U55Yh7mpFE8NhE7GiRwGsi7bzF8meoA8io6ZC1jfWm7AnVCPLld1DjPna4y/kbm4Djw1emH56h2oN6VFNzIKOOCI6DFCTKj48cvN6m9jtQC64yAjcXrjrnoBu/94VbDymTPSZvHs/A6RgsT0gZqC1M/46AJcJKx7mbW8RPL5m+e8HKpeusXbmNI1AFDHBkmZHzFpO9p3fkJSNLqEQsfgc6uhCQJRgy7qlF2ypXHynMEfy33/gbubc6XKsT2+MAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-04-30 04:42:59","box":1},
{"id":74,"question":"Nicotine Polacrilex","answer":"Thymophylla setifolia Lag. var. setifolia Lag. [excluded]","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAHVSURBVDjLjZPLaiJBFIZNHmJWCeQdMuT1Mi/gYlARBRUkao+abHUhmhgU0QHtARVxJ0bxhvfGa07Of5Iu21yYFPyLrqrz1f+f6rIRkQ3icca6ZF39RxesU1VnAVyuVqvJdrvd73Y7+ky8Tk6n87cVYgVcoXixWNByuVSaTqc0Ho+p1+sJpNvtksvlUhCb3W7/cf/w+BSLxfapVIqSySRlMhnSdZ2GwyHN53OaTCbU7/cFYBgG4RCPx/MKub27+1ur1Xqj0YjW6zWxCyloNBqUSCSkYDab0WAw+BBJeqLFtQpvGoFqAlAEaZomuc0ocAQnnU7nALiJ3uh8whgnttttarVaVCgUpCAUCgnQhMAJ+gG3CsDZa7xh1mw2ZbFSqYgwgsGgbDQhcIWeAHSIoP1pcGeNarUqgFKpJMLw+/0q72azkYhmPAWIRmM6AGbXc7kc5fN5AXi9XgWACwAguLEAojrfsVGv1yV/sVikcrksAIfDIYUQHEAoPgLwT3GdzWYNdBfXh3xwApDP5zsqtkoBwuHwaSAQ+OV2u//F43GKRCLEc5ROpwVoOngvBXj7jU/wwZPPX72DT7RXgDfIT27QEgvfKea9c3m9FsA5IN94zqbw9M9fAEuW+zzj8uLvAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-11-07 01:48:00","box":6},
{"id":75,"question":"Indomethacin","answer":"Callistemon pallidus (Bonpl.) DC.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAQAAAC1+jfqAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAETSURBVBgZfcExS0JRGIDh996OFIQEgSRhTS1Bg0trw937B9UPCAT3hnJ1kYbGhrv0BxoaXSsMhBCsyUEcoiTKUM/3HU8Fce4Q+DyRZz5DcOkdiqIIiiAo7xiCMXs4HI4ZisPhOMcQOJQbOoxxKHm22UUxBBbHM1cRfw58GUtMIAieTIwgxAQWRclMEZSYwCIIGYsixASCYsl4pgiGwDFF+HWUaDopbfCGHRp+nCWSTktFXvFDOKyuNNYp4LhFriPPaXW5UWAV5Y6HNH+/dbHJIjN6NHlJzMnxWqNIDqFHh8/U7hiEJbp0+ar0m2a4MGFEjie6jCrtJs1y57FuI21R6w8g8uwnH/VJJK1ZrT3gn8gz3zcVUYEwGmDcvQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-10-15 00:55:25","box":6},
{"id":76,"question":"Trihexyphenidyl Hydrochloride","answer":"Erigeron glaucus Ker Gawl.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-11-20 09:58:27","box":3},
{"id":77,"question":"Metoclopramide","answer":"Sphagnum lindbergii Schimp.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAACtSURBVDjL7dIxCwFxHMbxX8mmDAa67tV4D7wDZTolMlzpn+QoouNlyMZ0Vyc5g1v/JQPdYlJGmb5egbpLNsOzfuqprwDyzeQPfABc08A1FdOSZlLQODlFL2OkARThGGIfLhsIujxtUcmBWVETe3AcQNCGaMG9KTo5MMprTkvYdsCzYD/kWk8D9LMK34ZoDqED6waHaooLL1uMR0vUzRJ9roneVUStymL8S/wR8AaM7e7IrixORwAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-08-28 12:36:32","box":1},
{"id":78,"question":"Oxymorphone hydrochloride","answer":"Dicranum ontariense Peters.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAIcSURBVDjLjZO/T1NhFIafc+/trdRaYk1KUEEWjXHRaCSik+E/cDHGzYXB2YHRhMRFY1SYmRgYHZ3VxIRFDYMraMC2hrbQXm7v9+M4UGobiOEk7/adN+9zvnNEVQEQkYvAGBDy/6oBm6rqAVBVeia30jRtGmOctVaPU5qmuri4+AaYAgJVHTKYNsa4drutnU6nr1arpY1GQ6vVqlprdXt7W5eWlvomMv/uw6tSofB4p+NOF0biYtc48tEAhXiuTZzh/s1xyuUyWZbhvWdlZeXt3Nzca14sf6zW6nXf7uzrcfq9s6sLy5+1Xq8fQQKmo1ZCvlAoyo+tXT5tPGO09IckM2zWznH3/AJ3rl5ACInjmGazifceay2VSgWASISSBaz3FIs1RnJlPF18vEG1keDVk1lLFEWICM45wvAfYqTKriqje0lGI01x2qFtuuwkKQ26oEKcCwnDEBFBRA6HfmBw8JWwl3o2ti7j8+u0TUKzcYkrY/n+wyAIEJEjSxEglLyH5r7j+tg8T1oVZr8GzE69JIoiFMiM7zeHYUgQBAMJVBGU77+eYoxhLcvIxnNk6w8xxvDo3hqH+yIieO+HEkQB/qe6bPL5g/cckCkDiBhjOJULhlCGDJIkXX2z+m3GeW4UCnExyxxxHIIOLNLk2WP5AaQXTYDb1tovgHCy8lEUzQS9g1LAO+f2AX+SZudcAjgZOOeJ3jkHJ0zggNpfYEZnU63wHeoAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-04-05 09:45:18","box":1},
{"id":79,"question":"ALCOHOL","answer":"Arthonia platyspilea Nyl.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAFUSURBVDjLrZM/SAJxGIZdWwuDlnCplkAEm1zkaIiGFFpyMIwGK5KGoK2lphDKkMDg3LLUSIJsSKhIi+684CokOtTiMizCGuzEU5K3vOEgKvtBDe/2Pc8H3x8NAM1fQlx4H9M3pcOWp6TXWmM8A7j0629v1nraiAVC0IrrwATKIgs5xyG5QiE+Z4iQdoeU2oAsnqCSO1NSTu+D9VhqRLD8nIB8F0Q2MgmJDyipCzjvYJkIfpN2UBLG8MpP4dxvQ3ZzGuyyBQ2H+AnOOCBd9aL6soh81A5hyYSGWyCFvxUcerqI4S+CvYVOFPMHxLAq8I3qdHVY5LbBhJzEsCrwutpRFBlUHy6wO2tEYtWAzLELPN2P03kjfj3luqDycV2F8AgefWbEnVqEHa2IznSD6BdsVDNStB0lfh0FPoQjdx8RrAqGzC0YprSgxzsUMOY2bf37N/6Ud1Vc9yYcH50CAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2025-01-13 00:33:54","box":5},
{"id":80,"question":"Natural Medicine","answer":"Morelotia gahniiformis Gaudich.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-05-21 17:20:43","box":3},
{"id":81,"question":"ethyl alcohol","answer":"Michelia L.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-02-24 09:37:34","box":4},
{"id":82,"question":"Serotonin","answer":"Heliotropium convolvulaceum (Nutt.) A. Gray var. californicum (Greene) I.M. Johnst.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAI1SURBVDjLpZPNS5RRFIef98NRG3M05gOaqMhCAoskEFtVO2kT5DZo1SZoW9EiFGrVok1/QhRGmlHYJoQy8wuJIoLQ0iH8nCGcMmzm3ntOi1edWbQJLxzOPZvffc7v3OOpKjs5IcCDkbVbqlx2KvtEBCdgRXBOcKJYJ1XhcFZxIlN3Lh7pCAFE9Wp3x+7k/7zc0zd7fJvAiSQB4v1XQBWcBXFgTHQvl8CUoWTAGH7fGMYYV1slsOWDwt4UiI1C7aZICUwJbBk+LwFgrKt44JxsCniwmAeViEQkInFbGchkAChvCqCq3H+5pOsbRh+OrKiqat/bZVVVffwuqp+MRfXgeJTzxQ29dG9KVTUiME4QVcIA+sdWCQKfgfFVwgCeTa4yunKbN4OCilAz3cPR7C7KJiLwt1pQIAw8uk+lCX240JmmxofzHWl8L6C15TC+H3DuZCYarZWKB8YJKhD68GI6z2ThLhNDiqoSvr+O73vMzecI/ICnEytkEz5KtYAVVJWaALraU4wNwaEDB/mWm6erPUXg3aSztRlxysxCkT2NtcRrw0oLViK1wPd49aEAwFwuh4fH8McCRkBEmV0s0tQQI9lYtz25EMBaG3ngw9ljScLgGmfakrz+VOB0W5KB8TxfF36SiMdIJeoQUQKfCoFxUQtt+xtY+rFBS6aeueV1ss0xvnwvkk1AoiFGuqk+Ig08RFSqPpKO9j6aOVF2EjfWYazDWcE4wTr7z11Y+/XnOYC303X+CyNCWo09HetwAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAQAAAC1+jfqAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAChSURBVCjPY/zPgB8wMVCqgAVEFP7/w/CH4TcY/gLh59ul9oLtdmZk+I8D7vn/4f+e//8hJqT/h+kGwqu/GA7oQIz/D7NiJiM22/8j3BD9/xdMPwQ+vyL1n+EfEEIVLGXEph9Jge9/JN1XfzPcAbrhH8NfhILNWEz4h2yCPZIJYP88fyf1D9mRB7G6AUmBAdQXYN1X/zB8AYfDebACRopjEwDsBmruXDxiUwAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2023-10-19 15:59:16","box":3},
{"id":83,"question":"senna and docusate sodium","answer":"Tricharia cretacea Vezda","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-12-01 10:36:45","box":5},
{"id":84,"question":"Zoledronic Acid","answer":"Opegrapha leucoplaca Müll. Arg.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAALQSURBVDjLbZNdSFNhGMf/55xtx6P7aG1rbiSbORwpm/QJQeGQPq/SFmiFFZjBQiiF6CboUrxIUqioKIO66SYRQVAiBIkiilJGyJQGrjl1pq42c+ecnfUcEQrdgd/Fed/n/3+e533el2lvbw8riuIiFnp7eytQ4AsGg98kSaqQZfn70NDQ7v/3NCT05HK5F8SVpqamfCEDEqt0Eyc372lIyBNnyF2ytXTLRSwPUc5DVIBW232U6YHmG+81JK4lqjYbsCScIB4SkY/ax0JGSAlssVXIC1YhCr9gEuYEURSniefE+JYKSGgkagnZpP2Kscwn7Ofugs15MbzUgPEVH0TxskzZGwlTIQOJiNKmz84DByx6rIjXkF71Yyl1HJHfNrV/hVBj7FsMaFHcMKg+Ya+AjimGjHJkTEnA+RIKI+GpKGLDYG8hAyNx2m631wzfjBeYAUstiJVqjBpbyOAXMRCNRmXvnYF9Ak1BygEiDbTF+gg79QwOBT5PUpWDFBfcYkDuOtooJ7gP2U7sQSN0U3HYlyfwxWbGm4VpGI1GfTqdrqqvr6/s6+vLJxKJ5Xg83hkOhx9wbre7QxUTvOFoqjTxdgSHtUZcvHAOTqcTBtMO0D0xOBwOVygUEjweD2OxWNTRHiMTrdpCinhFhIqn1uCXqnGkrg4d924hFf4Jp8MBn8+n4zhO19PTg9nZ2ZzBYBhpa2s7NTMzc1VtoYbE5wm3NV6EbXrzem8HLyn5wetphq43zGYzqAUkk0nQe/mj0WjOUkjGZDLxqgFppSc6ne5Z7N0aOPePdYOx26uMIjHo6upCSUnJ+lomkwHLsjxV06/+UwtrjN/vnySDXcSEVqttph5fBwKB0rKyMoUybZ+fn0ckEgHP83C5XKBxgyayFIvF2NHR0Tkmn//3AL1eL0eH5aOM/XSANhJx6kVYXFxsVRNarVY1szabzeboLJJUUcNfnRWk+01xXkAAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2022-09-17 17:13:18","box":7},
{"id":85,"question":"Estradiol","answer":"Polygala rimulicola Steyerm. var. rimulicola","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAGxSURBVDjLpVM9a8JQFL0vUUGFfowFpw4dxM2vf9G5newv6OIvEDoVOnUQf0G7CEYQHVzUVZQoaKFugoW20EUaTd5L+u6NSQORdvDC5dyEd+499ySPOY4Dh0TEK8rl8n0mk7lOJBIpVVWBMUaJAzCFEMA5B8MwPpfL5VOlUrklonegWq3qEr+c/2Nbq9VWHs9XkEwm0xLUy/Lzn5KbD1exaDR6FlpBURSq4/E4HJ2c4jMwmYpcw6vf31be2bAHQTPVHYEFyAr7VeEACzfAQKPuSmlCy7LINBcteifSx3ROWutzlCAZ3Z9Op9ButyEWi8F8Poder0drXTQ1SNUeqalt22EFQrgvC4UC5HI5mow1EjA/SjdEjEQiYAd+HV8BF5xwNBpBo9EgBZPJBDqdDimYzWbQ7XapmeA8rIDLiRjFYpEm4zTEfD7v19lslhSgJ2EFXBAOh0Oo1+vk/ng8Bk3TyBtd16HVarkrCRFWYFqmrwAzqMDzBhMVWNaeFSzT5P3BQJXI3G+9P14XC8c0t5tQg/V6/dLv9c+l3ATDFrvL5HZyCBxpv5Rvboxv3eOxQ6/zD+IbEqvBQWgxAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAKkSURBVDjLjZLfS5pRGMf7N3bxslsvtsWuJBi0i4UNRrtYIeIumuwHbAgvXa0mMWGjMDebmSzTQtNuXGZLZr5ZXRQUJjm1jWmGhT9Wr/1UQnQX351zNkbt3cUOPBzO4Xk+z/f5ntMAoOF87O/vc6VSiSd7sFAoiLu7u2ImkwkmEgl+eXmZ+zv/wmFvb6+JFPqPjo5wfHyM09NTHB4eolgsIp1OIxwO+30+X9M/ASSJI+GnRWdnZ6CQxcVFCIKAnZ0d5HI5BhkbG/NbrVZOAiBSeVEUUS6XWXcKqdd/oFavMxW0OJvNIhQKobe3l5cAUqlUkCZSSKVSQXQzC8uoB0M2NyLxDMhoSCaTiMVi0Gq1QQmAmCQeHBwwqbSrZdQNVygN53wBVv83VKtVbGxsMCUajUaUANbW1kRiIra3t1Gr1WAeccMeymNkroTBme8MsL6+jmg0CqVSKQUQw4JbW1usAx0jGk/j3YcvMPhySKaKyOfzDDA1NYW2tjbpCOR56DszwPT0NOLxOE5OTpihVPrk5CRWV1eh0+mgUCikJtrtds5sNs8tLCxgdnYWTqcT5A42m43tA46X4C1qPH57F6pXNyu3n1/TXQB4PJ52h8MR0+v1fgqIRCJYWlpif+G91wi99wECm8P4XBRgmn8Kpekq5M8uGVmx2+1uJ1EbHx9HV1cXp1KpoFar0draipaWFtx/fQszyUHMfDWDLmP4EUzhJxRQZQCXy8Xmo7ObTCYYDAZYLBb09PSA53nceXEdnzbtOL8+JoYp4Jd8Oic1jbq8srJC/zwCgQC8Xi8mJiZwQ3sZA4IGfUInK+4LdV5U0N3djY6ODvo81GE0NzdDLpejsbERMpkMVxQc7hlleCM8ZJ3pTs9/PPifIMn9JMpU9u+9n97/BG848JbqijsUAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2024-11-28 03:19:21","box":2},
{"id":86,"question":"ivermectin","answer":"Allium cernuum Roth var. cernuum","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-11-07 11:49:19","box":2},
{"id":87,"question":"Midazolam HCl","answer":"Campylopus atrovirens De Not. var. cucullatifolius J.-P. Frahm","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-02-07 14:56:40","box":3},
{"id":88,"question":"Oxycodone and Acetaminophen","answer":"Tortula ruralis (Hedw.) G. Gaertn., B. Mey. & Scherb.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-05-25 11:55:43","box":5},
{"id":89,"question":"Acetaldehyde, Ammonium causticum, Carboneum oxygenisatum, Chloroformum, Formalinum, Glycyrrhiza glabra, Hydrastis canadensis, Kali bichromicum, Lycopodium clavatum, Petroleum, Plumbum metallicum, Taraxacum officinale","answer":"Hexastylis virginica (L.) Small","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJzSURBVDjLpZNLbxJRFMf7AfwEfA5YunTDTnwk3RlfMWFj4qKpKyfV2EVjhMwAUUyb1gYqCdWgQmqkRToFaRoLBcoUEGiB8hoQpgzPcpxzgREfO2/y39yc/++87p0CgKlJXTKCQpJKklrS9Ejq0Z3iz/hJ4wVJyofrda1954Tx78fZg8ghHwpH+e29GPvGk2JmbFUtxmDsb4CR+aLVm6dCh0muUKmDIHahdz4gajQ7kCtWwbcX5hY3khTGjiFjgBLN4dh3odXuAR6x04eq0AVe0lm7T+4EsQPbgaBgdh4hREkA2BeWjZnHZsduCYo/OlCoDZWvtSFXbcuQjU0fd3+1gO0oEKCys8cMlo2nXO/A1SdeeBcoymbNnAfuGiOkGjyx1CnQNj+DXgSofd+OWOwZS0XTlcdeSR5Y9xchy7ckwBYBVBpdqDd7UKqJsLT2nkUvAqaDBxEeh4UBCMCMqOvzfmCcGdBQW3DHECbVnVRa0Omdw6pljUcvAeyHwgSAAdgrmq893SGZDa5juPzIDbeZISBTbklVdGFp+bUMUH/ZjbI1oQ0NsUcyELOUFStKFUUJ8JkAcLC4mXi2BrTZIregsrgTTCZXgcEASAYN5SbmZEEkQvNNOkza6/YHsPk1CpTpozxExQNrWev2Bji+3pI3gcbEaRPi+aa8TjQnpOz6FyvcLVN8uMbxQ6LfhijHJ69QqJ6RSmpnPVJNuiSS9aE5nq2CzmwVZmnnr4c0+ZQXLAFqxebg/MEEZAp1MhPsOZrmweUNwQK9yM3oP/z9lCc/071Xae3cSxfzzLjM0gYT/1zP8PM6MzurszM3mNi/P9P/fOefb4UIeuRftTUAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2024-01-21 05:27:05","box":6},
{"id":90,"question":"Menthol","answer":"Pseudocrossidium aureum (E.B. Bartram) R.H. Zander","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAALISURBVDjLpZNpMNRhHMc31ExNmjRTDdVMsxXLkntnTcmxJTKFMK6JnK1KcheKDDZXubbSoRdlNFFNGFTIbeiNsyjHnzI0ZrFk/621+21bx6wx9caLz/Pi+T3fz/Ob56AAoKwH2WAU2QyP+wNO6xKY3WgOsMseKJQvTrm6p0ohplzcuqR4/lsQ0QQmhzA0SxkUW6QPbv47xz9t3zBjd3ZeStu0g+OAFJGUESnUtYLwRqjHjyhqxxFCvVtE+dwxC84vc5ZklmV1dHnhrJUNlW9ty588ZS+wzSHiVwkMwxpAPRm/b0/kcOqF82/m5wyYpIBhwpXfyTCOyAjKLJT0Frji29sktD+xQgeX7ikrGoTVY3nhhJaJZFj/hFA+vD+YeMFOe7QwVhOF6c4yYHYUU53FaEm3Hl8UhNbKBKJdagVC1b0i0zPvyS3eRLayz7Didp+hSteb+fMT3XELwu8lGKtNg6DrNRaIRnQ9DSBlAr2QGsTo2euKlVUkC9t2JFNciUSKCwEFF0LMCi2S8LpjJWJBIwQDl8FrC8KXZ77oyXZDW7aD+qIguBrYsNEOCpv65VsPiE3Kn+y6DjHZgrl+L5AjHpj5HI2hPPPxKeNDH1cOUffKBwgpSk4iitLu5fDd9IOcsU9RS2FPkMPu4HfHoI9rSfalM4yk3aqtCA4HvcPjnTTz5XBkskZlZ0UIxIJ6kEO++D1yDtPSTnq5LJFjlh5/zTvQuVQBk3BtVWYEPc/7qjqvpzwaHRWZ+NHqjLkhD/Dar+FrrsXPqjSGJjNBe5CRSM9ZLbhYDgO2pp0+W8PqZQoLmCHQ+9AJNdFqaHpgg7oEo9E7/keOy24sWEON5q7NNg6jbV0R0APLQGeXQotdggR/HQhbciFszUJrkgWe+x0AK/AeaH6vligGzbdIxopAHmdTFZLjRRNV37YRVWVY1pVG6VD/9xv/AJGzmhVs7+fUAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2022-11-03 20:58:59","box":7},
{"id":91,"question":"Miconazole nitrate","answer":"Perityle ciliata (L.H. Dewey) Rydb.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAIpSURBVDjLddM9aFRBFIbh98zM3WyybnYVf4KSQjBJJVZBixhRixSaShtBMKUoWomgnaCxsJdgIQSstE4nEhNREgyoZYhpkogkuMa4/3fuHIu7gpLd00wz52POMzMydu/Dy958dMwYioomIIgqDa+VnWrzebNUejY/NV6nQ8nlR4ufXt0fzm2WgxUgqBInAWdhemGbpcWNN9/XN27PPb1QbRdgjEhPqap2ZUv5+iOwvJnweT1mT5djZKjI6Ej/udz+wt1OJzAKYgWyDjJWyFghmzFsbtcY2gsTJwv09/Vc7RTgAEQgsqAKaoWsM8wu/z7a8B7vA8cHD3Fr+ktFgspO3a+vrdVfNEulJ/NT4zWngCBYY1oqSghKI465fvYwW+VAatPX07IZmF7YfrC0uDE8emPmilOFkHYiBKxAxhmSRPlZVVa2FGOU2Ad2ap4zg92MDBXJZczFmdflx05VEcAZMGIIClZASdesS2cU/dcm4sTBArNzXTcNakiCb3/HLRsn4Fo2qyXh3WqDXzUlcgYnam3Dl4Hif82dbOiyiBGstSjg4majEpl8rpCNUQUjgkia0M5GVAlBEBFUwflEv12b/Hig6SmA1iDtzhcsE6eP7LIxAchAtwNVxc1MnhprN/+lh0txErxrPZVdFdRDEEzHT6LWpTbtq+HLSDDiOm2o1uqlyOT37bIhHdKaXoL6pqhq24Dzd96/tUYGwPSBVv7atFglaFIu5KLuPxeX/xsp7aR6AAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAK9SURBVDjLbZJPaFxlFMV/93vfmz/NjElpp5rEyUggVijWP9BKVYQacSVIdeWqUBXRjYILaXetRFC7caHFhXYjBsyiuIiIirXQja0UQcSWmjaZxMFk7CSZyfx77/vedZFpSEgu3Ls4HC73nHtEVdmpvvixctSG9udAhCh2r554bvDLHYmquq0/nJqZmLq8qLOLHa3Uujp99T/9aOrW5E7cbcCZr2/+8t3VJa23E+061dipduJEL/9Z09Nf3bx99kJ5aDNf7kr4dHr+USPy6xP7B1IPDveBCI2OB6A/a7AG5qodfvp9mZWWe+nkyyMXgPUFn3xbfndPf+rs33NzqCo+Ubz3OOeJnSN2HkGJnCNJlPEnD3N9oX3u9Cult+y56QU/Npwzj4/189fMLU48O8i+QgERiwJxIiTrbuFdxKnPL/HCoQJ786tvTnxTfsPG7bX58UeGSt1YiWNHYW+B6sefkclkNoyWwOJsQOa146Ag6mm31rh47UrZLtXdSOQSJiZv4LzDGIvk8gw9fBBSAdgArKFy5RpJAsvdAd47f523XxwhXyiWTLPrJR0annqsyEq9QQKkQwv9fZBNQ2hBTE+Esss2ObC/yJ6BNICYVscBMHpfjmPPH+X98xc3pUQ2NUz+8AfjzxxhdDiH9PJnm71X2QBGh3Kknz7MB5eyBL+tbgmcY4zjhw7S9uEW3Dbb6xeIgIsdUay8fuwINtxKdHHMjYU6g4V7sKHdONC0uh4FosixWGtQvDdPKhVui7wNQx4YzFNbaZA4hyqggm11nfpEZelOg2IhTzYTgoIC/q4DCgmK3ZXC7stTqdZpD2RBE7XN2j+z3ciVHro/K7msETEe05MkIlusXB+W0u58MvtvI6pXFyo2WqvOjb/z/e50vq/PpgOxNsAEQmDAGMHY3gLZkK3eRVF7dflOdWa+/D+ThmoKzy7qoQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2024-12-04 14:19:14","box":7},
{"id":92,"question":"Lamotrigine","answer":"Camissonia boothii (Douglas ex Lehm.) P.H. Raven ssp. desertorum (Munz) P.H. Raven","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAH8SURBVDjLjZPfS1NhGMdXf0VEQhDUhdCN4X0IYT8ghIJQM0KoC4vushZddLELKyRhQQkSFIKEGEkUCI2oxVhepG5zi1xbc0u3cDs7Z+ec/ezT+x62scmmHvhwDrzP93Pe57znsQE2cR0SdAm6d+GwYL/M1LBVBV35fF4plUqVcrlMK8Q6TqdzYrukJuiW4Vwuh67rdbLZLJlMhmQyaUnigVlC05f4+dbB0tQplp92DsnwPimQBaZpUigUrLtE0zQURSGVSqHF37DhGkVZeQdagszKLJ7HvZtNAhmuIQWGYaCqKps/ZkivPqCwPs/Gp0cYvjnKUTe+F9fMJoFoo96zfJZ9K+sLpP33qRhujPANtr7dJPhqmO/PBxX3+PljTYLtqImPpH13qZge9LUrmLEB1FU7sZd9jJw5MljNthYk/KLnxdFqeAjzdz9Z/z3Ck2fRE36qx9pakAjME1y4Lbb9GTMyTD52GUXsZO3ZadTkL6umrSD4ZZrAezvLH54Q915EjwywtXSH8FQf+t+I9V12FLwe6wE1SmjyAi77Qb6Kt3rGe9H+hKzwrgLH9eMUPE4K3gm8jpPMjRwlHfNTLBbr7Cjo7znA2NVOXA/PsThzi2wyah1pI+0E/9rNQQsqMtM4CyfE36fLhb2ERa0mB7BR0CElexjnGnL0O2T2PyFunSz8jchwAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAALvSURBVDjLZZJdSFNhGMf/5+zo2pyb5cdyxXRNW2WkhhJGXlReFEZEBV0UVARBIAiCXnojdFE3QUQR3k6iC6GIoK+LMDNBaVpOW04by/yYzuk8O9v57DnHJqteeM57zvue5/c+///zMpqmITv6+vpsqqp2KorSRLGDAhRxiiFZlu+2t7dv4J/BZAF+v7+OkvtdLpfHbreDZVnQN9LpNGKxGGZpEOh8V1dX4D8AJdto87PX660SRRHRaBQ8z+ung+M4OJ1O4+dgMDhNa4e6u7uFLIDTH7R4q7y8vEqSJIRCoRkq9wSt/dIBgiC4EonER4/H46qtFKqqmXBq+vlt8MvvwaTnrhoASmiyWq0Ih8MgyJm2trZITpWRnp6eFmbtbbChuhiWkitweOqRmPVh6nXvnSygVNecTCb199l/jbpc56+3ey7BXtSAeHgS+YyIQvtO2IrdDiYycF0bCvuwuGYxNJ+tGYFJk6ApMjRZJpPWUVTVDMeeU8jMP4GwwmDpWwpSWlxJCxtHOZCJFy8cBwMWjMlC82lAZcidbUjFhpFJBODwtiI99whsvow8WwXM/BhSfH5LY8ebEKefBGiQl5+CM5eAYWwEyMPCHClhVJQdPEfJD8HmyRDXPVgZHEWaX8LhjkmjnaxeJlS6C4qIxMQoEsERLEQmsRrPoKymFeJCL0z5GjLrFYgNfILz5DWoUmrLHwJI0GVoioQi314siSziCQskzY35L/dBVwl8fBeWB4ex3cuAK7BDk8QcAPVe0xSqQMLq1wDGxn/gwLGbMEc/IPRsEIFXcUy9fAfWtAaWU6laFXrOXwBotEgSiqor8X1mEeLEC3hqm1FQQN0Zn4LviJtOL6auiIbcXABnlENUVdY9mMBEaB73Hj9A475KWEvNaNrvIx9+QuKTKHRT+STKkJ0L0CWYd9+ApcIEf4vZaCHZTmCSJgpQhCQpzFChyqZfuvFbADGDmf5Ooyx9Q6dvhrw10w3bvFiKsvmug/6M39LTvtXHnYlaAAAAAElFTkSuQmCC","playedDate":"2023-03-13 07:02:26","box":7},
{"id":93,"question":"Velvet Grass","answer":"Lecidea furfurosa Tuck. ex Nyl.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAITSURBVDjLdZI/aNNBFMc/vySSpLZFg5QguvgHcXHTImQu6OQq6CDoIDjoIpk6dLHgKA7iIOjgotjNLqJCKXQpooMOFSlWGpRGU/NLLnf33nNIQtKmPvjyOO7e57537yVmRj9uvblmF09fYLW+jJgiKj0pUSNnD1V4svCUxTvvkn5NjqGIIaLWPSwqRNVeHsj7OFyyC+AjZhBEhiBdqWp3rxN2ADLDi+AjecbIZwoEiXgJeAkEieSzRYo2TvDh/w6Cj3P19fezV/OfKYV1CuZQNZqa5Zce5u0nJfg491/As2MfNlrxY7M4dXucsVMYGRJtMxkajG9/4WD9QfPyebcxXJP0uxCXj0xjLHDiYdmyk2isQ/yLSYqJgyQBCTRXqzXxXCpfsZUdf2ASqhy9W7bcASz+AWlj4npK0c5PTFMKJ2+WwzbVkSdo9JXs/jNY3MbU9dTpyWHaQsNvMmNThJTKSBdUpWSZHKZt0E5PbiBxIE2wQPSURgGiYBHUD6z3b5eBI6xD9HvMgUapW2hgFnZZdwMIivgWoU19FBDckmytkCTZnfally2QyRRpb36n1WBpBCCO+ebqvZq6LcgWMIuY9JygJLkJokv4+vJ1rZ0yPzIHAJuPkhsSmJs4d728r3QcEsNiivgG6Y811p4v1topszMv7PGeAIBv95Np36AaHRWJlEIHXIu6S1kSYX7mVXeA+vEP7PyqQia3ZfwAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2025-01-12 03:30:57","box":3},
{"id":94,"question":"isosorbide mononitrate","answer":"Baptisia perfoliata (L.) R. Br.","questionImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAIHSURBVDjLpZPPS9RRFMU/3/GbmhVBWVJGLSQoi5AIM+o/CCowBKVFP3AZ0SKUFlELiaBNhNugEKTIIRFc1iJFs2iRm8QoSiIdQ2Z0Zr4z8969t4U644ALwwuP++57j3PuO5wbmBmbibDvffKeGZ1iekBVEQWviogianjRNUsQb4jqx54rh5sBQjW72dq8o/Z/WO+//Hai2IGo1gIMfn+OV48Xj1OPE1fK4ot33Wd6cE6q1gAsa9DReGND7Jmcx3kpaSCiAPSPJDYEcOHULgprAfwKAED7ub28Gp2j7Wxd8WxgfI7WllL9dzFX3oETRc0IK2BgLEFFRYz4eIIgBrGVR4MTCTBjSwhH62souBIAjwdnLJUtWPxDwszM3qzk1Xg9NltWT/9OWeHaVTMzzIzgYfyndU08BUCjPJrOIKk0klpEkotIKo2mM4zER1GgcX81h253otmImuGhIHR+WQNruwQixHJ5gmxEmM5gmSwWRaS6H3HxdB359g40G5HcXY1UVuFOtljoVZeZe5+ty6xRHoDhz/Nw5wkNeyrZd/k8ms2xc/JTwN2+KVtYytvbL/NmZvZucr7szwNj5Zp8/ZW0hSNNRQ1CJ4qZcfzgdv4sRDTUbeXHbLo4C8fqK5maSZV54db1Xn1RMpKNPuifbiqIbnNecF4QrzhRvPh1zZRcyg2t7oPNjvM/JWOW3I/zgm0AAAAASUVORK5CYII=","answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAGSSURBVDjLlZO7S8NQGMVb/weRgoI4iIuCVuoiuBfBwUFwaosPqJODk5OLBVutSlMsuDg4OVWkYO3o4Cha/BNS+qLP9K3HnEtT07f94HATcs8v33eSawBgUGtSlVmVZYimVY3Ro8nQBJgrlUq2Xq9/NxoN9JL6HD6f76oTogEsNBeLRSiK0lIul0Mmk0E8HheQWCwGSZLaICwjAdxQLpdRrVbFShUKBWSzWSQSCQEolUrgSwKBgIB0AWjWRAAN+XweyWSya6RmJsY2gDpGawOvObc2SiqVEp3Istwf0Ck9hJ0wj3Q6/X+AHsJxmAlBIwGoWq0mciGEGhnALkJvDzgK2LB3sQH7mRWrjtmbgQCaNAVf73HyYMdTVMK7HIb3xYkt7zxWDkyeoQC273BbEfy8RPDrGixPZBfeyD4B5aFfgVo/XkQoegt9PX5IBEAP+OmXwdrhDNxhB1xhmzC7nm1/HTR/x2U1ZUXd3PMw+YOn2PTM4Ty8I97MlfcigyZgipBBR3lhe/zO4jQpbJvrkn3CT+8vh7avwsYhJlIAAAAASUVORK5CYII=","playedDate":"2023-02-06 05:03:27","box":7},
{"id":95,"question":"Amethyst Rosa Clear Skin","answer":"Atriplex glabriuscula Edmondston var. glabriuscula","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-08-03 12:32:34","box":5},
{"id":96,"question":"ibuprofen","answer":"Paspalidium Stapf","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJUSURBVDjLpZNbaJJhHMZHUES51SoiqssWm5SMQekoFwvnYR4RP02dh/yMMhJpW3PaFOuzURfNi8GUDusw3QGDgl0k0Y3QcbjVqtsY3cVAu9uMwqf3ey+EwXBFFw/vgef58X94eesA1P2P1r284DDfDp/ajUhHPQZOCuBr3wXWrLv/VwAf64pFtM0YO3sUN1U7MOo+gr4OAdzSA2Cd1pENASGjGKO2JgyQ0A3TIRJuQJw5DF/HXhha91Q2BJw/3ojLaiHGr2gwwp6A/VgjrhqbYW0/CKZtJ0b6zmyvCRhU7ltdfH4XxfcT+P76AeYf9ePrs2tYmB1DVLP/56eHF7fUBCQcre9Kc5NYLmSx8nGKaJruS/NTuOMRFWpWaJP7tkql0ux4oBPlwj2sfnlKtfIhg8mBTojF4iei0+e2rQtQKpUNKpWKU6vVSKVS6OnpwcQQQ6XRaOidTqfj93HiFawBkOCmYDB4izfypmQyCavVimw2i0wmA5PJhOHhYXg8HnR3d1dkMtkggWyuAkjwEsuySKfTMBgMMBqNsNvtyOVyyOfzsFgs0Gq1sNlsiEajcLvdFblc3lcFLAw1/16eHUQ4HAbHcdTkcDhAJqPjMwwDr9cLl8sFv9+PYi6Kt/0t5SpgMdJSKb24Tg2JRIKCSCVq5iv19vYiEAggHo9T2I+XHOaCwkoV8PmxPzQfavrldDqh1+upkVcsFqP9+an4M+mPrq4uLERFZZLh1rzC0rSvnnRsIs/4ivRdIuOXFQoFePEhshYlEskbs9ks/Dbjq6/5G/9FfwAGy37p9rgYIQAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2024-06-08 17:32:28","box":7},
{"id":97,"question":"meradimate, octinoxate, octisalate, octocrylene, oxybenzone, titanium dixoide","answer":"Pedicularis macrodonta Richardson","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-07-22 21:48:18","box":5},
{"id":98,"question":"Aspirin","answer":"Astragalus peckii Piper","questionImg":null,"answerImg":"data:image/png;base64,iVBORw0KGgoAAAANSUhEUgAAABAAAAAQCAYAAAAf8/9hAAAABGdBTUEAAK/INwWK6QAAABl0RVh0U29mdHdhcmUAQWRvYmUgSW1hZ2VSZWFkeXHJZTwAAAJUSURBVDjLhZPPS1RRHMU/997nzDihTx0zFxrRxkqyQKNaBBGCWzetXUhYCUKLfrhtEdFGCqEWQf9AuK5FQouiokWrFoYuBioZ480o47x57/5q0cw4ReUXzvKce8/3fI/w3gMghBgCDgGK/08JKHrvHQDeexoi4/V6vaK1tsYY/zfU63W/vLz8EDgCSO894sKtF2Z4IKcS5XHG4qzHGEdeKDaKEasPpnDOkaYphUKBra0tVlZWHs3Pzy8BxSCXzzJ+cpC1qEaaGoy2OOMYKXSytl5CSon3HiEEAGEYMjMzsxAEAXNzc0vSGmsq2zFHuzpIYk1SN4z0dVKuxOAsSimklC2BTCZDLpdjdnZ2ARiQ1pibqx++plE55nghz4n+PFF5l1dvNrhx+TRSSpRSZDIZKpUKURRRKpVaGxX23VD4fnPs+bGe4uQBVcVZTznO8M1PcerSXVBdWGt/g3OOMAwJguBs4CyLZ0bHJkXfHZxLkGabXr1N1+ZL4s/3yY/dQynVjBohRDM1AKTTtWuifxqrK9i4iN1dx8YbyL4Jdj4+aRGbVpRSBEHQEgis0d3Sg7dVsDW8reF1BYQiKe/seW28rJT64wfG4X2Kt/Evsqvh7S7YOjrZO7RmlO1kAGl0uuP1DjjdEInBW7yponV361pbBCmRUrYJVPXj+MszhOxAZg8ic4MI1cOPT2/Jj179bXntaFn7/pQwiVisRVx3KV06BeN6Cc9d4fD0bYJ8+K9SuSAIzou2Nk4kSfJaKZUD5D6NdNbaWjabvdguMNyo837k5lig9BMTlFjmy9KhMwAAAABJRU5ErkJggg==","playedDate":"2024-06-04 21:53:35","box":6},
{"id":99,"question":"Prochlorperazine Maleate","answer":"Loeflingia squarrosa Nutt. ssp. squarrosa","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2023-11-26 14:45:27","box":1},
{"id":100,"question":"MENTHOL, METHYL SALICYLATE","answer":"Begonia cucullata Willd.","questionImg":null,"answerImg":null,"playedDate":"2024-07-26 07:40:19","box":6}]